[If you don't turn yourself in,
your limbs will rot and you'll die]
[All characters and events are fictional,
and any resemblance is coincidental]
[Scenes with children and animals were filmed
safely under professional supervision]
[Central Veterans Hall]
This recent redevelopment and reconstruction
reform bill has drawn strong reactions.
There are many saying that
it's finally a bill that reflects reality.
Association officials are also welcoming it,
saying negotiations have become much easier.
How frustrated must they have been?
The times are changing fast,
but the law couldn't keep up with them.
Even after the policy took effect,
your approval ratings have stayed strong.
At this rate, you might even want to start
thinking about a future presidential run.
No, right now it's more about
public sentiment than the presidency.
Is the interview we did
last time airing today?
Yes, it'll be on air in 10 minutes.
Let's watch it.
The prime suspect
in the Kangseng Serial Murder Case
which once plunged
the entire nation into fear,
[Serial Murder Case: Suspect Identified]
has been identified 33 years after the crime.
Wait.
Switch back to that channel.
Sure.
Police said at a briefing this morning that,
following a re-examination
by the National Forensic Service,
they are investigating
after being informed that
[Prime suspect: male inmate in his 60s]
an inmate's DNA matches evidence
from three crime scenes.
The suspect is a man in his 60s,
Mr. Lee, currently incarcerated...
[Episode 5]
Sun Young, can you hear me?
Ji Won.
Yeah.
Why am I here?
Don't you remember?
What happened to you?
Well...
Someone was chasing me.
I tried to run away from that person...
Who was it?
I don't know.
Ki Beom...
What happened to Ki Beom?
We don't know yet.
Sun Young, where are you going?
I've got to find Ki Beom!
Sun Young, you...
Is this that punk?
I found the owner of the handkerchief.
This is Sun Young's handkerchief?
Sun Young made this herself.
The only person who could have
something identical to this is Ki Beom.
So he only covered his face in front of me?
Why?
[Restricted Area]
Sir!
What happened?
Well...
We lost him.
[Surgery in progress]
Doctor,
how is he?
The surgery went well.
Fortunately, there is no organ damage,
so he is in stable condition.
Infection is the main concern,
but we'll monitor him for now.
These are the patient's belongings.
Prosecutor Cha went there to deliver this...
[Police Officer ID: Kang Tae Joo]
Did you not know you were pregnant?
It seems like it's been about three months.
- Pregnant?
- Oh dear, you didn't know.
And the baby? Is the baby okay?
Yes, there's nothing to worry about.
Fortunately, there are
no signs of concussion.
As long as the scrapes on your legs
are treated well, you should be fine.
If you feel dizzy or develop headaches later,
make sure to get checked.
- Okay.
- Thank you.
Oh, Sun Young...
Oh, Sun Young, Sun Young.
Don't tell my brother, please.
I'll tell him myself later.
Alright, alright.
Kang Sun Young.
Who is it? That punk?
Tae Joo.
Who's the culprit? I'm asking!
You, hey!
What are you doing
with someone who just woke up?
Answer me!
I don't know. I didn't see him.
Are you sure?
Why would I lie?
You were with Ki Beom.
Why are you bringing Ki Beom up?
Are you seriously suspecting him?
Are you out of your mind?
Then what about all this?
Where did Ki Beom go?
Why did this happen to you?
I'll explain. Stop pushing me.
So Ki Beom locked you
in a warehouse and left on his own?
He said he would handle everything himself.
I went after Ki Beom a bit late,
and someone started following me,
so at first I thought it was the police.
I thought they were tailing me to catch
Ki Beom, so I tried to shake them off.
Then I fell into the ditch.
That's all.
I don't remember anything after that.
Kang Sun Young.
If you're lying just to protect Ki Beom...
It's all true, Tae Joo.
Are you sure?
What happened to Ki Beom?
We're still chasing him.
Ki Beom was going to turn himself in.
I stopped him.
What?
Hey, what were you thinking...
You should've told me.
I was going to.
But when I went to the police station,
you weren't there.
And they said Jeon Kyeong Ho might die.
- What am I supposed to do, then?
- Die? He won't die.
That punk woke up.
No need to worry.
Oh, thank goodness.
But he's not the problem right now.
Then what is the problem?
[Kangseng Jaeil Hospital]
Don't worry about Sun Young.
I'll stay by her side.
I'm counting on you.
Isn't it strange?
If Ki Beom were the culprit, he wouldn't
have locked Sun Young in the warehouse.
Tae Joo.
The Ki Beom we knew...
Ji Won.
I'm going to erase the Ki Beom I knew.
That's better for him too.
Whether he's the culprit or not...
[Kangseng Jaeil Hospital
Nighttime Emergency Room]
You know it, right?
The reason why Ki Beom is on the run...
Tell me, what exactly is going on?
Ki Beom is...
a suspect in the serial murder case.
What?
I thought you were my father's son.
But I can't stand brothers.
Friends are fine, though.
Si Young!
What on earth is going on?
It was you, wasn't it?
You did this, right?
You punk, you really did this to Si Young!
If I hadn't been drinking...
Call Cha Si Young's house, you punk.
There's no one at his house.
What do you mean no one?
Si Young lives alone in that big house.
What about his family?
His parents and older brother
are probably in Seoul.
Are you interrogating me right now?
Call me when this punk wakes up.
That punk...
Does he not have a home phone number?
[Cha Jun Young]
Why would a superintendent
step in over a sergeant's resignation?
A superintendent?
You don't know Superintendent Cha Jun Young?
The youngest ever
to become a superintendent in Korea.
Cha Jun Young, Cha Si Young...
[Payphone Booth]
Hello?
Hello, is this Superintendent Cha Jun Young?
Speaking.
This is Sergeant Kang Tae Joo
from Kangseng Station.
Sergeant?
Why would a sergeant call me?
And at this hour?
I'm calling about Prosecutor Cha Si Young.
Prosecutor Cha Si Young
is currently in the hospital.
Why is he in the hospital?
He was stabbed during the arrest
of a serial killer suspect.
Jeez...
Wait, did he catch the suspect then?
No.
Are you sure that's the culprit?
It's too early to say for certain.
Yeah?
The surgery went well.
I thought you might want to know.
I'll hang up now.
Wait, how did you know I'm his brother?
Did he go around bragging about it?
I figured it out from the contacts.
Figured it out?
Cha Jun Young, Cha Si Young...
they're obviously sibling names.
Okay, then I'll hang up now.
What's with this guy?
He's only asking about the suspect...
His own brother got stabbed.
So he lost the suspect?
Hey, Kang Shik, it's Ki Hwan.
Do you know where Ki Beom is?
You don't know?
If you somehow get in touch
with Ki Beom or anything,
could you please tell him to contact me?
- Well, no, I mean...
- Oh, dear.
Alright, I'm hanging up.
Who is calling so early? Is it Ki Beom?
Oh, Ki Beom... yes, it's Ki Beom.
He just called to say he arrived safely
at his friend's house.
Oh, dear.
Did Ki Beom go somewhere?
Where was it again?
Did he say Haenam?
He once went to help out with farm work
at a friend's place there.
Tae Joo, what brings you here so early?
I was grocery shopping
and ran into him nearby.
Thank you.
Thanks to you, Tae Joo,
we got home without any trouble.
Don't mention it.
I don't get to visit often anyway.
- Ma'am, everything okay?
- Hey,
something good happened to you?
What good would there be?
Hey, did something good happen?
Did Ki Beom get caught?
Is that why you are here?
No, it's nothing like that.
Don't you dare mention Ki Beom to my mother.
I just said he went to visit a friend
in the countryside.
So you don't know where Ki Beom is, either?
Don't know. That punk...
I haven't heard from him
since that incident yesterday.
Is that guy okay?
Jeon Kyeong Ho?
Don't worry about that punk.
It'll be settled with an agreement.
What? Are you sure?
He's done plenty of wrong himself too.
Anyway, we need Ki Beom
for the settlement paperwork.
If you find him, send him to me immediately.
Okay, oh... thank you so much, Tae Joo.
Thank you, really.
- I'm leaving.
- Alright.
- Take care on your way.
- Yeah.
[Period for Reporting and Surrendering Spies]
He's not home?
Then, is there anywhere else he might go?
Even his family didn't seem to know
Ki Beom's whereabouts.
How do you know they weren't just pretending?
His family thinks Ki Beom
is running from assault charges.
His mother doesn't even
seem to know that much.
Since news of Jeon Kyeong Ho
dropping the charges was leaked,
if Ki Beom isn't the serial killer,
he'll respond to that.
So are you saying Ki Beom
might not be the culprit?
What nonsense are you talking about now?
If it's not Ki Beom, then who is it?
At the place they went to find Ki Beom,
Detective Kang's sister almost got hurt.
And the prosecutor was stabbed.
It can't be anyone else.
Right now, it's still
just circumstantial evidence.
The circumstantial evidence is piling up!
Sir, we should put Lee Ki Beom
on the wanted list now,
and search his house and the bookstore.
Prosecutor Cha Si Young
might have seen the suspect.
What if the person Prosecutor Cha saw
wasn't Lee Ki Beom?
I'm telling you, there's no way that's true.
Let's just wait until
Prosecutor Cha wakes up, okay?
- Sir.
Prosecutor Cha will wake up soon.
Right now, every second matters.
Right, sir.
We really don't have time.
- Sir.
- Darn it, you're too loud.
Just be quiet for a second, and let me think.
Okay? We don't have time, sir!
Oh, jeez!
Yes, this is Kangseng Police Station.
What?
A murder case?
Joo Hee, wake up!
Time to eat.
Why are you suddenly sleeping in?
Get up and eat. You have to go to school.
Her mother found her in the morning.
There are signs of strangulation.
Gosh. She's way too young.
The pattern is different.
[No entry, under investigation]
Was the front gate open?
They said it was open
when they checked it this morning.
Was she alone yesterday?
No. Her parents were sleeping
in the next room.
Wow, that guy is a total scumbag.
Her parents were right there,
but still he did that to the girl...
Under one roof...
He's completely out of his mind.
My gosh.
- What is it?
- Move.
What happened?
They say a child got killed.
- What happened?
- Is it true?
- A middle schooler was found dead at home.
- Why?
Don't tell me it's a serial case?
What?
Right? The place from yesterday?
Got you!
You little rat.
Hey, Do Hyeong Gu!
In 13 years on the job,
that was your best moment!
- Did you see that?
- That was cool.
- We caught him together, okay?
- I've got to pee. I'll be right back.
Hurry up and come back.
Ah, that punk...
What is he, a puppy? He just goes around
marking his territory everywhere.
Go farther away to piss, you punk.
Hey, where are you going?
Hey! Get him!
Hey, cut it out, you punk!
That punk!
Darn it, you punk!
If this was Lee Ki Beom's doing, shouldn't we
say something now? About yesterday.
Jeez, this is driving me crazy.
How does this even make sense?
Hey!
Oh my.
What is all this nonsense?
Why did our Joo Hee die?
I didn't hear a thing while I was sleeping.
I'm her father,
but I didn't even notice
my own child dying right next to me.
I was... I was sleeping just next door!
Gosh... what kind of father am I?
Wait...
What are we going to do about poor Joo Hee?
How can this happen to her?
It's all my fault!
I killed her! I killed her!
Why would it be your fault?
It's the darn cops' fault
for not catching a single murderer.
That's right!
How many times has this happened now?
Is this even a place where people can live?
We can be careful outside at night,
but what if we're killed in our own beds?
Exactly.
People are getting murdered day after day.
How can anyone live like this?
Exactly!
- Sir!
- Come on!
Why are you doing this?
Wait, hold on.
- Wait, just a moment please.
- Sir.
- Please calm down. It's okay, calm down.
- Sir...
I'm the one in charge.
The lack of progress
in the investigation so far...
Yes, I have no excuse.
As the chief, I bear
the greatest responsibility.
But our detectives
and officers are all doing their best
day and night in their respective roles.
So if you could just trust us
a little longer and wait, we will...
Wait for what?
Let's just leave.
Please stop this.
We will...
- We will definitely catch the culprit.
- When?
- What are you doing?
- Do it properly.
[Kangseng Police Station]
- Hurry up!
- What is it?
Jeez.
What's with this mess?
What's going on?
The superintendent's coming. Line up quickly!
The superintendent's here!
Superintendent!
Put this on first.
Dae Ho, take that!
Okay, he's coming.
One moment, please.
- The superintendent?
- Everyone, line up!
Everyone, attention!
Salute!
Welcome, sir.
Why is he here?
I don't know, either.
Should we go in too?
Even His Excellency
made this decision with great difficulty.
He acknowledges all your hard work.
Don't take this assignment as a demotion.
Think of it as a chance to rest.
Oh, this tea isn't bad.
Give me some water.
Si Young, are you awake?
I said water.
Water, water...
Excuse me! Doctor!
The wound has healed well.
But avoid getting it wet
when bathing for now.
So can I be discharged?
Let's decide after checking tomorrow.
Alright, then...
Thank you!
You're incredibly lucky it wasn't worse.
You wouldn't wake up for so long,
so I thought you were in serious trouble.
What about the culprit?
Not caught yet.
More importantly, the whole Kangseng
went crazy while you were asleep.
The National Police Agency holds Kangseng
Police accountable for the serial killings
and demotes Park Eun Kyu
to the Jeolla Provincial Police Headquarters.
Wow, they replaced the police chief
in the middle of this?
Even three team leaders? What's happening?
Superintendent Cha Jun Young,
the youngest in the country,
has been appointed as the new chief
of Kangseng Police Station.
[Cha Jun Young]
Public trust in law enforcement
has hit rock bottom
due to the sluggish investigation so far.
We plan to deploy
large-scale manpower and set up
a new investigation task force.
You said you'd expedite the investigation.
When can we expect visible results?
It's difficult to give a specific timeframe,
but if we move away from a passive approach
and act more aggressively,
I believe we can restore
our damaged reputation.
Are you saying you're confident
you can restore trust
from the victims and their families?
On the honor of the police...
Wow, looks like some big shot's here.
He's just a cop though.
Good work.
Don't feel so down.
This horrific case is happening in the place
where you were born and raised.
You must catch him on the honor
of Kangseng Police, no matter what.
Yes, sir.
Sir.
Drive safely.
- I'm leaving.
- Okay.
Everyone, attention!
Salute to Mr. Kim!
Thank you for your hard work!
Let's head inside.
Where on earth is that punk Kang Tae Joo?
He doesn't even know what Mr. Kim
did for him. What an ungrateful punk.
Where did he go?
Hey, what are you doing here?
Were you waiting for me?
Why are you grinning like that?
You like getting transferred that much?
If I'm being demoted to the seaside,
how could I not be happy?
You know how much I love sea fishing.
Take this.
What's this?
This still reeks of eggs.
Why do you keep wearing it?
It bothers me.
- Does it smell?
- Obviously! You think it doesn't?
Since when do you have money?
Just...
I made quite a bit.
But isn't it a bit oversized?
Come on, you should be wearing that size.
That way it covers your belly too.
You're not even that skinny anyway.
I don't have a belly, you punk!
Tae Joo,
you're a good detective.
However,
don't try to handle everything alone.
Work with your colleagues.
From my experience,
your colleagues are your greatest asset.
Remember that, you punk.
Thanks. I'm off.
Nagging till the very end.
Take care, sir.
Autopsy results show
the victim was sexually assaulted
and then strangled to death.
Any clues on the culprit?
Yes, what appears to be the suspect's hair
and bodily fluids were found at the scene.
Once again, the suspect is identified
as a male with blood type B.
That's it?
Yes.
There's nothing new at all!
This is why people in charge get fired.
- Sorry, sir.
- Jeez.
Kang Tae Joo!
- Yes, sir.
- What do you think?
Is this also a serial murder case?
I don't think it's a serial murder.
Why?
Unlike previous cases, this one involved
a home invasion, not an open-area attack.
The victim was 14,
which is different
from the previous age range.
There's also no sign of the serial killer's
usual binding pattern.
Is that so?
Are you okay?
What's wrong with him now?
Do you need to take a dump?
Pardon?
Or do you have something to say?
No, I mean, it's just that...
Around 11 PM on the night of the crime,
suspect Lee Ki Beom was spotted
near victim Lee Joo Hee's residence.
He was probably running away
after committing the crime.
This case...
is clearly a serial murder.
Yes.
That's all from me.
These guys are unbelievable.
Huh?
You hid something that important?
Have you lost your mind?
Fine, I admit I messed up.
But how could I have known?
That he'd kill again while fleeing?
Darn it!
Around 11 PM, that's right after
the attack on Prosecutor Cha.
Right.
So he escaped the scene
and hid in Lee Joo Hee's house.
The alibi checks out perfectly,
and the timeline fits as well.
Kang Tae Joo!
Even now, you still think
Lee Ki Beom isn't the real killer?
Even with this?
His Excellency sent me.
It's also Father's will.
Father did?
Whether it's democratization or what,
the aftermath of last June's protests still...
Now, it's even about to
influence the upcoming by-election.
But you know
how crucial this election is for Father.
So Father wants us brothers to take the lead
and solve this case together.
"Us brothers"?
Yes.
Does that mean you're accepting me
as your brother?
Hey, have we ever not been brothers? Huh?
We share the same father's blood.
Now I'm starting to feel hurt.
Get up, get up!
You little punk.
He'll do better next time.
You know how smart Si Young is.
Right?
Si Young...
Father, I was wrong.
Please, just one more chance.
Give me just one more chance, please.
Please, just once.
To live as my son in this house,
you must prove worthy.
Remember that.
[Cha Si Young: 2nd Place]
Don't take Father's words lightly.
You'll be out otherwise.
You don't think you're
the only illegitimate child, do you?
Jeez.
Anyway, take care of yourself.
Let's do our best.
I'm leaving.
Take care.
"Us brothers"?
There was a time I desperately
wanted to hear that.
But now?
I'm already too old
to play the spoiled little brother with you.
Sir!
I heard a new task force is being formed.
Has the new team leader been decided?
Why would that interest you?
What, trying to get yourself in line early?
I have zero interest in that.
Isn't that a position
meant to stand up for subordinates,
even if it means taking the blame?
Please use your influence
to bring in someone like that.
That little punk...
Wow!
Hey, what did you say?
- Hey...
- What did you say
to make him so pissed?
Tell me.
So I can use it too later.
- Did you see it?
- Yeah, obviously.
His face completely crumpled
after you said that.
No, the culprit!
- Did you see him or not?
- Ah, it hurts.
I'm still a patient.
I got stabbed, remember?
Did you see him or not?
I didn't.
What?
Were you expecting some other name from me?
Are you still not convinced?
That Lee Ki Beom is the killer?
You've been like this from the start.
Ever since
you labeled Lee Ki Beom
as a witness rather than a suspect.
You're excessively favorable toward him.
- It's not that.
- Then what is it?
If Lee Ki Beom is the culprit
in the attack on you,
there's an unexplained gap
in his movements that day.
It really feels like two separate people
were in the same place that day.
Ki Beom is one, and the person who kidnapped
Sun Young and attacked you is another.
- But...
- But what?
Lee Ki Beom was spotted
near victim Lee Joo Hee's house.
Right after the estimated time of the crime.
I was wrong.
The evidence confirms
Lee Ki Beom is the killer.
Thanks for saving Sun Young.
I haven't told her yet
because she's still disoriented.
I'm sorry...
to you,
and to Ms. Sun Young.
I said I'm sorry.
Sun Young, what's wrong?
Did you have a nightmare?
Oh, just a dream?
Is it because you're worried about Ki Beom?
Ji Won, something feels off.
He left like that,
but he hasn't contacted me once.
That's unlike Ki Beom.
Honestly, that's been bothering me too.
I'll check at Ki Hwan's place.
He might have contacted home.
Let's go together.
Yeah, alright, let's go together.
Well... hello?
- Oh!
- Is Seok Man home?
Seok Man's out right now.
By any chance,
has my younger brother been here?
No, he hasn't even shown his face lately.
Tell Ki Beom to come visit.
My daughters are looking for him.
They're asking when the handsome guy
is coming. They're going crazy.
Okay.
Aren't you getting off here?
I'm... I'm sorry.
Oh, for heaven's sake.
Where do you think you're going, you punk?
Oh, you punk... seriously.
Hey, hey!
Get up!
- Darn it!
- Ki Beom!
This punk has no fear.
Hey, go ahead first.
How dare you run! Are you out of your mind?
You punk.
Darn it.
So you know that punk, huh?
Don't say a word about what you just saw.
Unless you want to die.
Hey, you punk!
Speak, you punk!
I said say it.
Say it, you punk!
Spit it out, you punk!
You stubborn punk!
Hey, spit it out!
You killed them all, didn't you?
You punk!
This guy is seriously getting on my nerves.
Hey, haven't I seen you somewhere?
You punk, seriously...
Hey, go easy on him.
Don't worry. I didn't touch his face.
He still won't say where the handkerchief is?
He just keeps saying he lost it.
We got the search warrant.
Really?
Oh, how touching!
Did you come to pick me up
because I'm getting discharged?
Sign this.
What is this?
A search warrant?
I need to catch the culprit.
As soon as possible.
How soon?
Before the new task force is set up.
Before your brother gets to put everything
he's prepared into motion.
Hey, I like that.
I like that a lot.
Looks like Kang Tae Joo
got it approved. Darn it.
When we suggested it, he ignored us.
As long as we got it, it's fine.
What should we do?
Alright, let's go!
Hey!
Speak, you punk!
Ma'am.
Sun Young, what brings you here?
I came to ask if there's been
any contact from Ki Beom.
Why do you care about that?
Didn't you say you were done with Ki Beom?
Ma'am, this is important.
Where is Ki Beom now?
In Haenam. He's at a friend's place.
Really? Are you sure?
He called and said he was doing fine.
Isn't that right?
Jeong Sook,
did you really get a call from him?
Well, actually...
Wow, the weather's really rough today.
Alright, line up.
If you find anything suspicious
during the search,
seize it immediately. Got it?
- Yes, sir!
- Okay.
Excuse me, what's going on here?
What? Is that really true?
So you haven't heard
from Ki Beom at all? Not even once?
Why are you only saying this now?
Ki Hwan told me not to tell you,
afraid it would only worry you.
- Let's go inside.
- What are you doing right now?
Darn it. An insect.
Honey!
Ki Hwan!
Mr. Jang, what are you doing?
Ms. Seo, you're here too.
Are you Lee Ki Beom's mother?
- Yes.
- This is a search warrant for Lee Ki Beom.
We ask for your cooperation.
- Search everything thoroughly! Every corner!
- Yes, sir!
No, wait...
Oh, my. Why are you doing this?
- Mother.
- Why are you doing this?
- Search it thoroughly!
- What are you doing?
What are we going to do?
Where should we start?
[Kangseng Bookstore]
Hey, don't miss a single spot.
Search everything!
- Yes, sir!
[Please claim your lost items]
[Capital]
So he's even been acting
like a darn communist...
Wait...
Stop right there, you punk!
Got you, you little rat!
[Please claim your lost items]
Just leave it to other detectives.
You don't have to personally get involved.
Hey, you punk!
Jeez, your stubbornness...
Shouldn't you at least tell us
why you're doing this?
Move aside, unless you want to
be hauled in for obstructing justice.
What exactly did my brother do wrong?
What's with all the questions?
Your brother Lee Ki Beom
is a serial murder suspect.
What did you just say?
Serial murder?
That's ridiculous. Even a passing dog
would laugh at that!
- Tae Joo!
- Detective Kang, what took you so long?
- Prosecutor Cha!
Tae Joo, perfect timing!
These punks are completely delusional.
They're calling our Ki Beom a serial killer.
My boy couldn't even hurt a fly.
How could he kill anyone?
Tae Joo, get through to these idiots.
First, calm the mother down.
Ki Beom really is a serial murder suspect.
He is currently on the run.
Have you had any contact with him?
We must find Ki Beom, ma'am.
You think Ki Beom's a suspect too?
Hey, answer me!
I said, do you doubt him too?
- Yes.
- What?
We have grounds for suspicion,
so we have to investigate.
If Ki Beom's been framed, I'll prove it.
And if he's the real culprit,
I'll make sure he's caught.
So if you trust Ki Beom,
trust me and cooperate
with the investigation.
This is the suspect's room.
Start the search here.
You...
You little punk, I'll...
Mother, Mother!
- Let go!
- Please calm down.
Won't you let go? Let go of me!
This is all your fault!
If you, as the eldest,
had chosen your friends wisely,
would this have happened?
Please stop, ma'am.
Don't touch me.
I was the one who fed you and your sister
when your own mother didn't!
And now you, of all people...
are trying to destroy my son?
- Mother!
Mother, are you okay?
Mother!
Take your hand off me.
Sun Young, you...
Don't tell me it's his...
It's Ki Beom's child.
Jeez.
You... seriously?
Have you lost your mind?
That guy is a serial killer!
How could you carry his child?
Don't say that!
Ki Beom's not a serial killer.
I remembered what happened that day.
I clearly remember the person
who dragged me away from behind.
- It wasn't Ki Beom.
- Don't talk nonsense!
There weren't any streetlights
in those fields where you were taken!
You couldn't see anything!
He was limping, like he was injured.
I swear it's true!
Enough!
Even if you're telling the truth,
I can't believe you.
You'd even twist your own memories
to protect Ki Beom.
- Tae Joo.
- Sun Young.
Go wait in my car.
Ji Won, but...
Nothing you say will change anything.
Don't waste your energy. Just go.
Go on ahead.
Go.
Are you seriously not going to
investigate this properly?
I'm doing this now because I'm trying
to investigate properly.
If I hadn't trusted that punk and hesitated,
it never would've come to this.
Give me a break.
Hey, don't fool yourself.
You're not some warm-hearted guy.
You acted that way simply
because there wasn't enough evidence.
Because things didn't add up.
There were gaps you couldn't explain.
That's just who you are, Kang Tae Joo!
Jeez.
- Huh?
- What is that?
This...
This punk.
Look at this.
Detective Kang!
I knew you had some connection
with Lee Ki Beom,
but I didn't realize you were this close.
[Wedding Reception]
Hey, it's been a while.
You're late, Tae Joo.
I had something to deal with,
so I left Seoul late.
Where is the groom?
He went to the restroom.
I think he's got an upset stomach.
He must've eaten everything they gave him.
No wonder.
- Hello!
It's been a while.
Everyone else is getting married.
When are you going to?
Do you at least have a girlfriend?
- Well, that's...
- Tae Joo!
Why are you so late?
The wedding's already over.
I came all this way,
so you should at least thank me.
You punk...
Here, this is for the wedding.
Thank you!
Tae Joo, let's take a picture together.
We should at least have one.
I'm dressed like this.
How am I supposed to take a picture?
I'll take a picture of you two.
Ki Beom, you should take one with us.
Yong Tae, take a picture of us here.
Alright.
Just one shot, please.
Okay, look here.
One, two, three!
December 13, 1987.
If you were this close, shouldn't you
have recused yourself from the investigation?
Hey, Kang Tae Joo!
That punk...
He's running now that it's not in his favor.
Choi In Sook, Choi In Sook...
[Choi In Sook's Records]
Choi In Sook, missing on December 13, 1987.
Estimated time of the crime, 8:30 PM.
Ki Beom was with me at that time.
How did this happen?
Who would've thought it would turn up there?
- Right.
- Oh, Kang Tae Joo!
You are already here?
Sir, we found evidence
that Lee Ki Beom is the culprit.
What?
Here.
What is this?
[Please claim your lost items]
Inside this,
[Park Ae Sook]
we found this.
This belongs to Park Ae Sook's?
Yes.
We just came back after confirming it
directly with Park Ae Sook.
She said she lost it on the day of the crime.
[Resident Registration Card, Park Ae Sook]
Where could the prosecutor be?
[Capital 1-1, Capital 1-2]
Maybe at the office?
Got him, got him!
I'll go report and come back.
Yes, sir.
Park Ae Sook's handbag
found in the bookstore.
That's evidence that Ki Beom is the culprit.
But the photo found at the house
proves Ki Beom has an alibi.
Two pieces of evidence are telling
completely opposite truths.
What is this?
What am I missing here?
Tae Joo!
What did you mean earlier?
Why did you say our Ki Beom is a murderer?
Ki Hwan, let's talk later.
Hey!
When did you start suspecting Ki Beom?
Don't tell me it was from
when you came to my house?
The settlement was just an excuse,
and you came to find our Ki Beom?
Is that it?
Answer me, you punk!
How could I not suspect him?
What?
A victim's belonging
was found at the bookstore,
and the last places victims Yu Jeong Rin
and Kim Min Ji visited were your bookstore.
And the suspect was wearing
Ki Beom's handkerchief!
So how could I not suspect Ki Beom?
What came out of the bookstore?
Ki Hwan, this is...
It doesn't make sense
unless Ki Beom is the real culprit.
If not Ki Beom, then who...
Someone besides Ki Beom who can enter
both the bookstore and the house.
There is...
another suspect.
Mr. Lee Yong Woo, have you been well?
Where is he?
Professor Kang Tae Joo
has returned to his main job.
He needs to finish his research paper too.
Are you saying that meeting me
is less important than his paper?
It's not like that.
Lee Yong Woo has clammed up again.
He's gone back to how he was
when we first met.
He's not only hostile,
but he's also being really spiteful.
Why did you quit, anyway?
You really built a good rapport
with Lee Yong Woo.
Now, that kind of thing
should be handled by active-duty officers.
Don't think about using an old man like me.
Please tell me how to do it, sir.
How to make Lee Yong Woo talk?
Lee Yong Woo has already made up his mind.
He's decided to tell the truth.
So it won't be difficult.
Oh, and...
Lee Yong Woo asked me
to pass this to you, sir.
He said it was a gift or something.
A gift?
[Murder: 12+2, Rape: 19, Attempted: 15]
What is this?
What are these numbers?
[Murder: 12+2, Rape: 19, Attempted: 15]
The truth.
The suspect is a Mr. Lee
residing in Kangseng...
Lee Ki Beom has just
made his first confession.
Ki Beom, is it really you?
Answer me!
Was it really you?
So that's why you tried
to kill Sun Young too?
But she's not my family.
Are you the real culprit
in the serial murder case?
Is this actually Lee Ki Beom's statement?
It's all just things we already know.
And some of it is completely wrong.
Unlawful confinement and assault!
If Prosecutor Cha finds out
everything you've done...