=No Pain No Gain=
(Adapted from the Qidian novel)
("Losing Money to Be a Tycoon"
by Qingshan Quzui)
=Episode 22=
(This story is purely fictional)
Everyone is here?
Let me make the introductions.
He
is Lawrence.
Mr. Law.
And this is the renowned director,
Director Zhuang Dace.
Director Zhuang.
Mr. Law, I have long admired you.
This is the screenwriter of our show,
and the head of Feihuang Pictures,
Huang Sibo.
Mr. Law.
Yellow.
I really admire your work.
Mr. Ma. Have some water and have a rest.
No, it won't be necessary.
Ocean, there is really no need.
After all, today you are a bit...
You know?
I know.
Mr. Ma's motion sickness today
is quite serious.
I was not like this before.
Maybe today, it is because of
this aircraft model...
Mr. Ma.
I do not care who he is.
A set visit is just a set visit.
Have a drink and leave.
Why should he use my makeup artist?
Careful.
Mr. Lu.
The entire crew is waiting.
Can he afford to delay everyone?
Mr. Lu.
(Mr. Lu Zhiyao's Private Makeup Room)
This way.
The wind messed it up a bit.
Please fix it again.
Thank you.
Who is this?
Why is he sitting in my seat?
Mr. Law.
This is our male lead.
Mr. Lu Zhiyao.
Mr. Lu.
This is from Tengda,
Mr. Lawrence.
Hi.
Nice to meet you.
Lu?
Do you have an English name?
(Sima Fu)
My hair is quite soft,
so spray a bit more hairspray.
Mr. Lawrence.
What's up?
We have been waiting day and night
for you to arrive at last.
You have no idea how much we missed you.
We were really hoping you would come.
Really?
Yeah.
- Wishing us a successful start.
Now, let us welcome our producer,
Mr. Sima Fu,
to the stage for a speech.
(Northern Continent.
Wishing a Successful Launch)
Thanks to Qisheng
for hydration and moisture.
Qishenghua, the skincare brand
that pioneered
herbal skincare.
Thanks to Zhiguang
for myopia prevention.
Thanks to Ziguang, the lighting brand
that pioneered
purple light eye protection.
Thanks to Xiquan
for the healthy drinking water.
Thanks to Yuanxin
for formaldehyde-free living.
Thanks to Kelin
for the beauty in full bloom.
Many thanks
to all those who support us,
our eighty-three sponsors.
Did I hear that right?
We have eighty-three brands?
So he is not here
to interfere with the old project.
He is here to place new brands.
Wait, are all eighty-three brands
being placed into our show?
I believe
we will definitely surpass
Universal Studios.
Let me ask something.
Who is he?
No idea.
Why is my umbrella shading him?
It is extremely hot today.
Thank you all very much.
Now, let us get back to this project.
From the early stage,
the writing and polishing of the script,
to the later casting decisions,
including when we
decided to start filming,
and even the future production process,
I believe it will all
be a difficult journey.
I think everyone gathered here...
If I were to present
Her Highness Qishenghua's
Hydra Lock Moisture Radiance Mask,
how would you respond?
Wait.
Stop.
What kind of lines are these?
Where is the screenwriter?
Have the screenwriter come over.
Coming.
What is going on with these lines?
What is wrong?
What is going on with your lines?
Do not tell me this was demanded
by the brand.
You are the screenwriter.
If others tell you
to change it and you obey,
then what are you even writing for?
Exactly, Screenwriter.
Can you not have at least
some artistic principles of your own?
Right?
Yes.
This will not do.
Exactly.
This really will not do.
Everyone, am I right?
- Yes.
See?
Fine.
I will revise it right away.
Technical adjustment.
Everyone, take a short break.
Hello.
What is going on with you all?
What happened?
- Mr. Law...
- He is driving us to the brink.
Wait.
Isn't Mr. Law doing a set inspection?
How is that affecting you over there?
Mr. Pei.
Before he went to visit the set,
he also arranged work
to insert brand advertising
into the game.
Lv worked overtime until he collapsed.
Is Lv all right?
Yes, he is fine now.
The doctor said
he is still young,
and severely sleep-deprived.
Lv, come on.
Say hello.
Mr. Pei.
Mr. Pei, I am fine.
I just need to sleep a bit.
Then, let him rest a little longer.
Let him rest.
All right.
During this period,
if anything happens,
inform me immediately.
The afternoon is off.
Everyone goes for a medical checkup.
Any issues will count as work injuries.
The company will cover it.
Thank you, Mr. Pei.
But we cannot take time off.
Mr. Law said that,
even if he is not at Tengda,
he will still hold video meetings
to review the work.
Mr. Pei,
what are we supposed
to do if this keeps up?
(Unknowingly,)
(the nightmare
of life is repeating itself.)
(In the past, because of Mr. Law,)
(and his special business ties
with Tengda,)
(I gave him face,)
(and let everyone suffer.)
(Now that it has come to this...)
It is time to use my trump card.
I will send you a document.
Follow this from now on.
- Fuhui Job-Security Survival Manual?
(Fuhui Job-Security Survival Manual)
Does this name sound a bit off?
(You withdrew a message.
Re-edited it)
(Pei Qian withdrew a message.)
(Pei Qian: Anti Law Work Guide)
- Anti Law Work Guide?
From now on,
follow this
to carry out your work.
(Pei Qian: From now on, follow this
to carry out your work.)
Hurry.
Mr. Law is calling a video meeting.
Anti Law Work Guide, first principle.
Respectful but slow.
No problem, Mr. Law.
Any ideas you have,
feel free to raise them.
We guarantee we will get it done.
About how long will it take to finish?
We still need to discuss it.
Then how long will the discussion take?
How about we discuss it first
and get back to you afterward?
Anti Law Work Guide, second principle.
Make an effort,
but still cannot do it.
Lawrence, here is the situation.
The game development process
cannot be quantified.
However, we
are already improving process
based management
and resource integration,
doing everything we can
to em...
Em...
Empower the product...
That is feasible...
Within the three months you requested,
we can integrate
all potentially viable plans.
Integrate.
This arrives at the current
optimal solution.
Yes.
Your eyesight is not great.
You should get yourself
a pair of glasses.
Alright.
What you are talking
about is the process,
but what I want is the outcome.
Result.
What I just said was that
we have found the optimal solution
for the current situation.
We are now shifting
the focus of our work
to improving process-based management
and resource integration,
overcoming the challenge that
game development cannot be quantified,
and striving to follow your plan
to complete the integration
of all potential solutions
within three months,
thereby empowering the product.
That sounds much more professional.
I totally understand now.
Anyway,
could you go into more detail
about how you will ensure that the game
becomes a hit after launch?
We will roll out
full funnel deep marketing,
using a matrix-based strategy,
to create a brand new
value conversion model.
Perfect.
Exactly what I had in mind.
Proceed.
Alright.
Mr. Pei is really something.
Where did he
even learn all these tricks?
Let me tell you,
someone like Mr. Pei,
who has survived both Fuhui
and Sky Fire,
is rare these days.
He even teaches us personally,
without worrying that one day,
we might use these tricks on him.
These skills are probably just
the tip of the iceberg for Mr. Pei.
(Tengda Games)
Mr. Pei.
This...
You are finally back.
While you were away,
we really relied on
the Anti Law Work Guide
you gave us.
It was truly effective.
We all owe you our thanks.
Save the thanks
for later.
Is this helicopter
really that nauseating?
Mr. Pei.
Over here.
Mr. Pei. You need to come take a look.
Sima and Mr. Ma are arguing.
Ma Fu. Let me make this clear.
It was Mr. Pei who told me to hold back.
I am not afraid of you.
What did you just call me?
I called you Ma Fu.
Say that again!
Ma...
So what?
Loss.
You know how much effort it took
to secure this client.
We have to take
this case.
We cannot.
This case clearly states
that I must hand over
all my social media accounts.
And most importantly,
this case
forbids me from dating.
No relationships at all.
Even Lu Zhiyao is allowed to date.
Why am I not?
Is that so?
Who is he seeing?
Isn't it that...
Is this really the time for gossip?
This contract is indeed
going too far.
As for the money in the contract...
Mr. Law,
this is not about money.
Do not assume money
can settle everything.
Do I look like someone short on cash?
Ma Fu.
Guys,
let us all calm down.
This case
is genuinely important.
It affects our long-term future.
Okay?
Shall we talk?
There is nothing to talk about.
There is nothing between us
worth talking about.
Ma...
Mr. Law.
How about this?
Take a moment to calm down.
I will go talk it over with Ma Yang.
Call me Ma Fu?
Ma Yang.
Qian, I was not snapping
at you just now.
This Ponytail Live thing
has been torturing me
these past two days.
I am really on
the verge of breaking down.
Ma Yang.
About this Sima Fu,
he is actually from the Sima family...
Forget it.
This is all on me.
If you do not want to take this case,
then we will drop it.
I will talk to him
and figure something out.
You need to figure
something out quickly.
You have no idea
what I have been through these two days.
Did you watch my livestream?
Look.
You did not even watch my livestream.
If you have never suffered their pain,
do not preach kindness to others.
If this keeps up,
there is no way
I will ever be able to date.
Enough.
I am going out to get some air.
No.
Out.
It is a black cat.
I am allergic to it.
Okay?
Mr. Pei.
Mr. Lawrence said
he is allergic to cat fur,
and wants Yintang
removed from the company.
Loss.
This is an office.
A pet in the office
is not a good sign.
Mr. Law.
Yintang is not just any black cat.
It is our company mascot.
It has witnessed
Tengda's entire journey...
from the very beginning
to where we are today.
And look at Yintang's forehead.
Jet black and glossy,
radiating nothing but good fortune.
It is a sign that our company will
continue to grow and prosper.
Well, okay.
But if it is staying in the company,
it has to create value.
Here is the plan.
Set up social media accounts for it.
Bring it into
the broader Tengda content matrix.
And boost its IP value.
Yintang,
let us put up with this for now.
Once I get in touch with Mr. Sima,
I will get Sima Fu out immediately.
Tomorrow,
I will buy you more canned food,
and some dried fish too.
Please make sure to
like, comment, and share
to support Ponytail Live.
(These yoga pants
are extremely stretchy.)
- Yes.
(You can see
how well they fit the body.)
(Take a look at this pair right here.)
(You can honestly say...)
(Can...)
(They photograph
beautifully at the beach.)
(We only have ninety-nine orders left.)
(Just ninety-nine orders.)
(The current price is only 19.9 yuan.)
Where are you? I am coming over.
The key point is,
the fabric barely wrinkles.
There are still some creases.
End the stream!
But...
Change your clothes right now!
Wait...
Mr. Pei, we are still live.
End it immediately!
Please hold on.
We are still live.
Hurry up!
What are you doing?
Sorry, Ma Yang.
I did not realize
this was how you streamed.
Change your clothes now.
End the stream.
Where am I supposed to go?
There are tens of thousands watching.
You cannot just leave them hanging.
No, but you cannot stream
this product either.
Wasn't this one taken by Ma Fu?
The quality is terrible.
I have no choice, either.
If you are going to stream it,
just tell the truth.
If I tell the truth,
this product is done for.
Then, we destroy it live.
Destroy it live?
(Winter Fairy. Bare Legs Miracle.)
Guys.
This bare leg miracle product...
Do not buy it.
You think their color
looks natural, right?
Come on.
Turn off the beauty filter for me.
Everyone.
Now. Quickly.
Does it still look natural now?
It looks fake as hell.
The color of this product
is extremely unnatural.
And when you wear it,
it looks completely fake.
(Key selling point. Natural skin tone)
It is full of creases everywhere,
like a durian mille crepe.
They do the most marketing online.
They run the most ads.
(Read from the script)
Yet, the price is the highest,
and the quality is the worst.
Do you know how much
(Pause)
they sell this for?
One hundred eighty!
Shut up.
Pause? What pause?
Everyone.
Do not send me gifts.
I, Ma Yang, am not short on money.
Just now someone
sent me a gift.
(Keep talking and I'll sue you.)
Kick him out.
Everyone.
Watch carefully.
I, Ma Yang,
will never coexist
with fake products!
This lotus leaf and winter melon
rose green tea
not only helps slim down,
but also nourishes the skin.
I will cut it open right now.
There is no winter melon inside at all.
(Product testing only. Do not imitate)
These rose petals are loose,
and the lotus leaves are shredded too.
Without dosage,
what benefits are there to discuss?
The Northern Realm
has been buried in sandstorms lately,
and yet, they claim you
cannot live without this herbal
pearl cream.
It is a complete scam.
Do you know why the ingredient list
is written entirely in English?
It is meant to fool you.
Why can't I use my Qingyuan True Flame?
So it is the Black Sesame Divine Pill,
steamed and sun-dried nine times.
Your internal power
comes entirely from this?
This is fraud.
You all need to know,
black sesame is forty-six percent fat,
and twenty four percent carbohydrates.
After eating it,
there is only one bodily change.
Your face gets rounder
and you gain weight.
Transition.
(You think this color
looks natural, right?)
Director.
(Come on, turn off the beauty filter.)
Director. I have revised all the title
pages related to product placement.
See if there are any issues.
(This fabric is completely ordinary.)
(What is this brand called?)
(It is called Winter Fairy.)
(They do the most marketing online,
and run the most ads.)
(But their prices are the highest.)
(Because of additives.)
(It is all meant to deceive you.)
(Even miracle pills
are not that effective.)
(You need to understand,
black sesame is forty six percent fat.)
Do you
never go online?
All those embedded brands
were completely destroyed
by your Mr. Ma
during his livestream.
The title pages...
This whole production has to be reshot.
Lu Zhiyao said
you need to rush and redo
everything related to his scenes.
Not reverting to the original version.
He
has come up with
some new ideas.
Mr. Ma, ever since we switched
to destroying products on livestream,
those unlicensed sellers
have shut down
their online stores and vanished.
Mr. Law even called them startup brands,
but they were all junk products.
He said all the products involved
have been pulled for rectification,
along with public apologies.
Good.
Honestly, it feels great.
Mr. Ma,
quite a few brands
have reached out to us,
saying that as long as
we do not mention them
during the livestream,
they are willing to sponsor us.
Sponsor us?
Yes.
Is that not basically protection money?
Do they think we are the mob?
Put together a blacklist
and send it to me. Right now.
It is already done.
I'll send you all
their requests immediately.
Okay.
Sponsorship, huh?
Post it.
Mr. Ma.
You posted all
their private messages online?
That...
I am someone now
with a serious number of followers.
Do you know
what my fans call themselves?
What?
They call themselves Aima.
They say I am a fighter.
They say I represent
the spirit of Tengda.
What if Mr. Law finds out?
We have Mr. Pei backing us.
Why would I be afraid of him?
How could you let Ocean
destroy the products?
My entire business plan
has been completely ruined.
You cannot even imagine
what we are facing right now.
Do you know how much
we will have to pay in penalties?
An astronomical figure.
First,
we have to refund everything they have
already paid.
Second,
we have to pay Ponytail Live
all the breach penalties
under their cooperation agreement.
On top of that,
we also have to pay the penalties
under Tengda's strategic
partnership with them.
They are even going to sue us.
This whole thing is
a complete
disaster.
Are you finished?
Then let me say a few things.
First,
some of those products
involve false advertising.
If it goes to court,
we are not in the wrong.
Second,
many of those unlicensed products
do not meet standards at all,
so there is no breach on our side.
Third,
all your ridiculous schemes
are honestly no longer my concern.
But have you looked
at this quarter's accounts?
Even if we lose
and pay all the penalties,
it still costs less
than your personal expenses.
By the way, Ms. Xin,
all those helicopter expenses of his
will not be reimbursed by my side.
He can bill his father for that.
You are crazy.
One last thing.
From now on,
speak Chinese when you talk to me.
Otherwise, I will not
respond to a single word.
Do not forget this.
Every decision I made
has your signature on it.
You are the one in charge of Tengda.
All the compensation payments
will ultimately fall on you.
So you can speak properly after all.
Ms. Xin.
Go take a look
at this quarter's accounts.
If he can actually make
the company lose money,
I will praise him.
But starting now,
please stop tormenting
everyone at Tengda.
Look at this.
Mr. Law really knows how to burn money.
Personal expenses,
losses from the production shutdown,
and penalties from destroying
products on livestream.
If Mr. Pei can keep this up,
you'll be
the biggest money loser of all.
Whether who ends up the biggest loser
doesn't matter anymore.
What matters is that I cannot tolerate
him for even one more minute.
(Why do I still
have this ominous feeling?)
(Profits: Private Kitchen, Sloth Gym,
Shared Phone Booth, Returning to Shore)
(Four Wall Apartments, Zhongdian Web Fiction,
The Divine Mountains and Seas)
(Losses: Feihuang Pictures,
Ponytail Live)
(Tengda Total Assets)
(The Foundation Stone.
Toward the Future.)
Ideas cannot be industrialized,
but they can form ecosystems.
With IP at the core,
we build a new model
of cultural production,
and move toward a stronger
cultural industry ecosystem.
Together, we build an IP ecosystem.
(The Leader of the Big IP Era)
(Exclusive Interview:
Lawrence, IP Industry Trailblazer)
(Lawrence's Business Empire)
(Exclusive Interview
with Ponytail Live Founder Lawrence)
(Sima Fu: In the future,
let's share even more shining moments.)
Such a coincidence.
I did not expect that my last order
before leaving the country
would still be with you.
What a cursed coincidence.
Loss.
I genuinely do not understand
what you are talking about.
But that does not really matter.
As an
entrepreneur,
my personal entrepreneur IP
is already firmly established.
Anyway,
since you enjoy driving so much,
I do not mind leaving this car with you.
IP?
You are really asking for trouble.
Let me be clear.
I have rheumatism.
I cannot drive your car.
Then, just leave it at the airport.
Someone will come pick it up.
(Cui)
(Qian, just giving you a heads up.)
(The apartment at Mingri Apartments)
(has finally been rented out.)
At least, the mortgage pressure
can ease a bit now.
Still, who would rent that place?
You have a new order.
Please handle it promptly.
(Instant Order)
Airport designated driver requested?
Had a few drinks on the plane?
License plate...
(Order accepted)
A one two three...
four?
Are you the designated driver
who accepted the order?
Yes, I am.
May I ask
what your relationship is
with the owner of this car?
Sima Fu.
Sima Sui.
Sima Tu.
These names were
really chosen at random...
Wait, do they also have
an eldest brother
named Sima Wan?
You mentioned before
that Mr. Sima
wanted his sons to come here
and toughen up a bit.
But now it feels like
he sent me here to be the whetstone
for his sons instead.
Let me be clear.
That is not in my contract
with Mr. Sima.
Get in touch with him immediately.
Mr. Pei.
To be honest with you,
ever since Sima Fu arrived,
I have not been able
to reach Mr. Sima either.
In overseas,
his phone will not go through?
He was not kidnapped, was he?
Before leaving, Mr. Sima told us
that he had a very important plan abroad
and asked us not to contact him
for the time being.
A very important plan?
What kind of plan?
The boss's affairs
are not something
I am entitled to ask about.
One Sima Fu is already more than enough.
Who knows where
these brothers came from?
What kind of working style is this?
I understand everything you said,
but why do you have to be
the one taking responsibility?
Why can it not be me?
Excuse me,
sorry to interrupt.
Sima Tu.
Sima Sui.
May I ask what kind of work
you intend to do at Tengda?
Mr. Pei,
I have already thought through
my responsibilities
and how I plan to work
after joining Tengda.
I look forward to your guidance.
Here is the thing, Mr. Pei.
From now on, report directly to me.
I'll discuss things
with my second brother afterward.
Our third brother here
just likes to show off.
Please excuse him.
Qian.
What is going on this time?
Mr. Pei, as soon as I heard
something major had happened,
I rushed back from the set.
You said in the group chat
that two investors were coming.
Are those the two?
They are also surnamed Sima.
Are they related to Mr. Law?
They are not brothers
from the same family, are they?
Well...
They are Sima Fu's
second and third brothers.
Just like Sima Fu,
they are all investors in Tengda.
They may
be staying at Tengda for a short time.
Everyone will need to get used to it.
Sorry for the inconvenience.
No wonder you told me earlier
to cut Sima Fu some slack.
So when are those two leaving?
How did you even get involved
with a family like this?
Since when has Tengda
had outside investors?
Wasn't Tengda founded by us?
Alright.
Mr. Pei,
is Tengda facing
some kind of difficulty?
If funding is an issue, I can...
No need.
Our current investment allocation
is already fully subscribed.
And honestly,
those two can't be harder
to deal with than Mr. Law.
That's reassuring.
As Tengda continues to expand,
the issues we encounter
are bound to become more...
complicated.
Let's just take it
as part of the learning process.
Got it.
We all understand.
Mr. Pei, don't worry.
We can handle this.
We won't put you in a tough spot.
Just make sure
you don't push yourselves too hard.
- Mr. Pei,
- please call all department heads
- to the conference room.
- I want to speak with them directly.
Today,
the reason for this meeting
is simply
to meet
Tengda's core staff,
have a conversation,
and talk things through.
You're welcome
to share your thoughts.
No need to speak freely just yet.
Let me wrap up
today's meeting first.
This was mainly my idea,
so I will chair the meeting, all right?
What is Tengda's
strongest pillar right now?
It is the gaming industry.
The Divine Mountains and Seas
is currently
the hottest game on the market.
So we must
fully support its development, right?
Sui.
(Support The Divine Mountains and Seas)
You are getting a bit carried away.
What we need is
comprehensive and balanced development.
Every line of business
should become
(Balanced development)
a core pillar.
Tu, after all that you have said,
it is clear you
still have not figured out
what you actually want to do.
If you ask me,
we should focus heavily on games.
If you cannot
get your core business right,
and still want to try side paths,
is that really wise?
Listen to me, all right?
No, better listen to me.
To borrow one of your young people's
internet phrases,
dddd.
Those who know, know.
After all,
I do keep up with the times.
(My goodness.)
(This meeting is completely absurd.)
(These two Simas.)
(They are talking past each other.)
Aren't these all
memes from two years ago?
Mr. Tu,
Mr. Sui,
let us focus the meeting
on a single key point.
We were previously developing
version 2.0
of the Divine Mountains and Seas.
Why don't we first decide
whether to continue pushing it forward?
- Do not proceed.
- Proceed.
(Mr. Sima)
Hello.
The number you have dialed
is temporarily unavailable.
Hello.
The number you have dialed
is temporarily unavailable.
See? I was not lying.
There really is no way to reach him.
With his sons
causing this much chaos,
he has the mood to focus
on some so-called major plan?
When he gets busy,
he does tend to vanish
like this.
Then, what usually happens every time
he disappears and comes back?
What happens is that
his group
moves up to another level.
Whether his group grows or not,
I honestly do not know.
But if this keeps going,
Tengda is going
to be completely wrecked.
(You have a new group message.)
(Lin Wan: Mr. Sui has
confirmed that the new 2.0 version)
(of the Divine Mountains and Seas
will be released tomorrow.)
(Lv Mingliang: Mr. Tu has confirmed)
(that the Divine Mountains and Seas)
(Version 2.0 will be postponed.)
(Lin Wan: Mr. Sui
announces that Version 2.0)
(will still move forward.)
(Lv Mingliang: Mr. Tu announces
the Version 2.0 can proceed as well,)
(but he wants
to replace the illustrator.)
(Is that even possible?
We can't replace Ruan.)
(What should we do?)
Is this them doing actual work,
or just fighting each other?
Mr. Pei.
You said before
that these two brothers
would be easier than Mr. Law.
Turns out they
are even harder to deal with.
They do not dare touch us,
so they go after Ruan Guangjian instead.
Now no one dares go back to the office.
Everyone is hiding out
at the gaming cafe.
I was the one who brought Ruan in.
No matter what, we have to protect him.
Mr. Pei.
Say something.
Do not serve the food yet.
Even Ms. Xin is here.
You are sick of them too, right?
(Tengda Business Group)
(Sima Tu: The meeting will continue)
(tomorrow at 9 AM.)
(Business Group of Tengda)
(Sima Sui: The meeting will continue)
(tomorrow at 8 AM.)
Am I blind or what?
What is the difference
between these two groups?
The Tengda Business Group
was created by Sima Tu,
and Sima Sui is not in it.
The Business Group of Tengda
was created by Sima Sui,
and Sima Tu is not in it.
Seriously?
Are they picking a fight on purpose?
Who could keep this straight?
I need to change the label fast,
or I will send something
to the wrong group.
(Tengda Group Without Tu, With Sui)
Lv, you did not change a remark.
You changed the group name!
What?
What do we do now?
Change it back.
I seriously cannot believe this.
Mr. Tu, Mr. Sui.
Here is the situation.
Tengda has internal rules.
People do not start work this early.
How about we set
the meeting for eleven instead?
And one more thing.
I think our top priority right now
should be pushing forward
the new version
of the Divine Mountains and Seas.
We need to get everyone
internally aligned first
before asking people to work.
If we cannot even agree among ourselves,
are we not
just inviting others to laugh at us?
And also,
about our illustrator, Ruan Guangjian.
My suggestion is
that you take a look at his
social media accounts first.
He is verified, so he is easy to find.
You can review his art style
and his follower numbers.
After all, both his artwork
and the game itself
are very well received by players.
We should
be on the same page about that.
What is Pei Qian trying to do?
Not a single person
shows up during work hours.
They are pushing back against us?
This kind of unhealthy attitude
really needs fixing.
Alright then.
Cancel
tomorrow's meeting for now.
We will start
with employee one-on-one talks.
Employee talks are not the key issue.
Employee training is.
Start with employee talks.
Move on to employee training.
Talks during the day.
Training at night.
Starting tomorrow,
everyone will need to adapt
to a new work schedule.
We cannot keep being as lax as before.
Is this insane or what?
No, what is this supposed to be?
We're dancing on a broken beat
Exhaustion written all over us
Watching as the colors fade away
Your silence
It's a fortress and I'm running out
of ways to get to your heart
It's harder to see you
when I get too close
The buzzing in the air
The static's getting louder
Shadows dancing
Say you've had enough
I say I've had enough
I struggle on, holding back the clouds
With the city inside
Say you're holding on
I say I'm holding on
Can you see the weight behind
this pain, this smile I'm wearing
I'll never let it show
Curating the highlights in my story
Filter out shaky frames from my glory
All this noise and mess
Needs some stillness
Say you're holding on
I say I'm holding on
If you need to say goodbye,
just let it out, baby
I'll get by
Say you've had enough
I say I've had enough
If you're bearing the ache
of every single breath you take
And I'm watching him escape
I'm falling through the space
into the silence you make
Just a flicker in the dark
and saying out your name
All this noise and mess
Needs some stillness
Say you're holding on
I say I'm holding on
Darling
I'll gently feel your face
I'll reach you before dawn
I want you to keep believing
Darling
Let's take it slow and play our parts
And fool our hearts
In this static, this buzzing air