But the company's resources
should be used on groups with potential,
right?
No matter what the result is,
it's not just your own business.
Don't shoulder it yourself.
I got it!
What?
What is it?
This!
The 3 of us
stand side by side under the starlight.
Let's go with a bright stage outfit.
It'll go well with the song.
[SE Entertainment,
CEO Mr. Lee's Office]
Of course.
Yes.
Yes, yes.
Of course.
Yeah.
Mm.
Yes.
Really.
Of course.
Yes.
I'm sure you'll be satisfied.
Yes, yes.
Yes.
Yebin.
What is it?
Mr. Lee.
This is the demo of our new song.
Can you have a listen?
Yebin.
I understand how anxious you are.
But I have to listen
to 5 new SESPA songs now.
We composed this song ourselves.
Please have a listen.
You all?
With what skills?
What about the mixing?
And mastering?
I'm...
really not refusing to help.
But the company's resources
should be used on groups with potential,
right?
If we can't achieve the profit goal,
we'll be disbanded.
Then work harder.
Okay?
Show up to events.
Appear on show programs too.
Sorry.
I have an appointment.
I'm heading off.
Oh.
Also...
All the best.
Yes, yes.
Bin.
Have some water.
Minah is thinking about the concept.
I tried making a melody.
Let's listen inside.
No matter what the result is,
it's not just your own business.
Don't shoulder it yourself.
[Wonder-X Member Dormitory]
I got it!
What? What is it?
This!
The 3 of us
stand side by side under the starlight.
Let's go with a bright stage outfit.
It'll go well with the song.
Yeah. It looks like it goes well.
Really?
Let's look at the outfits then.
It's too early for outfits.
We'll talk about it
after the producer is decided.
Okay.
I added a harmony
in the chorus.
Can you help me see if it fits the lyrics?
Okay.
Here I go.
It's amazing.
It's good.
But
I don't think Lee Sumin will make it.
So I'm thinking of reaching out
to all the producers I know
in the afternoon.
If all else fails,
I can ask my dad to help.
Just wait a bit more.
No matter what,
let's cheer up.
Yes.
We can do it.
Come on!
One, two, three.
-We got it!
We can do it.
It's okay.
We can do it, right?
Yes.
Not bad, right?
Yeah!
It's great.
Come in.
What is it?
Long time no see, Mr. Lee.
Yeah.
♪ Through the white curtains ♪
♪ Today's sunlight is shining gently ♪
♪ From my toes ♪
♪ The excitement spreads ♪
♪ It's not as strong as it was yesterday ♪
♪ I feel awkward ♪
♪ But it's okay; I can just be pretty ♪
♪ The trembling of my fingers ♪
♪ I hold my breath and call your name ♪
♪ Right now, we are like the first page ♪
♪ The moment ♪
♪ My thoughts I wrote carefully ♪
♪ I'll hold it tight
so it won't get tainted ♪
♪ It's okay not to run ♪
♪ I will collect these days word by word ♪
♪ Even the insignificant gaze ♪
♪ I want to keep it in my heart forever ♪
The melody is good.
I feel the sincerity in the lyrics too.
The company
will take this song.
Really?
Thank you.
What's there to thank me for?
It's a good song.
Bring the members
to my office tomorrow.
Let's talk about the composition.
Yes, we'll come tomorrow.
Unnie.
Did you find a production company?
Of course.
Mr. Lee said he will produce it!
That's great!
That's amazing!
Gosh!
We did it!
I knew it.
-Cheers.
Does anyone want to cheers?
Yes, let's do it.
Cheers.
Where's your strawberry?
Do you want some?
I'm okay.
No?
Let me feed you one.
No need.
Unnie.
I have one.
Grab Yebin.
Ji-eun, grab Yebin!
She only eats strawberries I give her.
You're ostracizing me again.
Isn't it good?
Add some strength
to the chorus with some strings.
If there's a piano accompaniment
for the intro,
it might be good. What do you think?
Sounds good.
Great.
This part too.
If we all belt a high note here,
it might be more impactful,
and it might be able to better show
our determination to never give up.
That's right.
Sounds good.
Yeah.
Minah.
Is there anything to change
about the concept?
There is?
I want to add a starlight string here
so that it goes better
with the arrangement.
The performance would be cooler too.
Sounds good.
Yeah.
Really?
It's great.
1, 2, 3.
Let's go!
We can do it.
The string idea is great.
Really?
I'm tired.
But the song is really nice.
Listening to it gives me energy.
Let's keep going for a while more.
There's only 1 week left.
We need to prepare singing and dancing.
We also have to film the MV in a week.
Right.
We can do it.
But it would be better
if you spun slower.
Got it!
You're doing well.
We can do it!
We're Wonder-X!
Come on!
Wonder-X, let's go!
You only have 7.5 million fans.
It's 2.5 million to 10 million.
There's only 1 week left.
Can you do it?
Yes.
The new song is in place.
The MV is also being filmed.
We also have plans to increase
our follower count
through social media promotion.
Promotion?
The company won't invest any more in you.
Your social media account
is full of anti-fans now.
They're all telling you to disband.
There are many other ways—
not just support from the company.
You can overcome hate comments
with skills.
Wonder-X can do it.
You must
keep your promise.
If you can't achieve your goal,
I won't be able to help you then.
Oh,
there are paparazzi
near the company recently.
Be careful.
Don't get caught.
[Wonder-X might as well just disband already. Wonder-X has truly hit rock bottom.
Has WONDER-X had enough of this drama? I never want to see them again. The recent songs have been absolutely terrible.
What kind of "idol group" is this supposed to be? They do nothing but make their fans worry.
They're just a group the company pushed out based purely on their looks. They don't deserve to stand on that stage.]
Girls.
We have to
do a live streaming this afternoon.
We have to show the fans
the choreography videos and new songs too.
Minah, I will leave the posting
and outfits to you.
Ji-eun, wrap up the melody composition
and play it for everyone.
Yes.
I'll do it right away.
I have the chorus I completed previously.
I'll clean that up.
I'm sure the fans will love it.
I'll make a impactful poster.
If I add a hashtag
#Wonder_X_never_gives_up
to emphasize our determination,
it might create a sensation.
There are fans waiting for us.
So let's work a little harder.
There are fans waiting.
Yes.
Yes. Let's do it!
We got this!