( Watch on Kissasia.vip & KonFlix.vip )
1912, OTARU
Thank you for coming!
SAKE
Hey! What the...
Watch where you're going!
What the hell is your problem?
Hold on. Ain't you a fine woman?
Get out of my way.
A feisty one. My kind of woman.
What the hell do you think you're...
What's it to you, old man?
Stay out of this!
Hey, what the hell is
your problem, old man?
Forget it. Let's get out of here!
Hey! Let's go!
Impressive. You haven't lost your touch.
Nagakura Shinpachi
captain of the Shinsengumi's second unit.
And who are you?
My name is Ichikawa Makoto.
I've come from Tokyo.
There's something I must ask you.
It's about the Shinsengumi.
Leave!
Please, wait.
I have nothing to say.
I'm not leaving until you talk to me.
It can't be anyone else. It has to be you.
You...
You purposely let those drunks
harass you, didn't you?
Please. I want to know
about the Shinsengumi...
No.
I need to know the truth
about Hijikata Toshizo.
Hijikata Toshizo?
He...
had the same look in his eyes as you.
Prickly and aggressive,
like a briar patch.
Or maybe reckless
like someone who would
charge right into one.
In case you get hurt, I sell medicine.
We called guys like that baragaki,
thorny brats.
That was Hijikata Toshizo to a tee.
Brace yourselves!
Come on.
I'll be sure to give you some medicine.
- Master!
You! A low blow? You coward!
The art of the sword is
for battles, isn't it?
In battle, who gives a damn
about fighting fair?
The gall of a mere merchant!
Come on, bring it!
Let me know if you need more medicine!
- Hey, here.
- Oh, thanks.
Are you always pulling stunts like this?
Yep. It's quicker to create the injured
than to track them down.
Right? There!
- Thanks for your business!
- Don't ever come back!
What a face. All right, my bad.
- Just get out already!
- Yeah, I'm going.
"The Shieikan dojo."
What a dump.
Hey. This is a dojo, right?
- Hiya!
Come on! Knock it off!
You little bastards!
You're supposed to fall.
Because they cut you.
Okita Soji.
Though normally gentle
once he draws his sword, he's a demon
a true sword-fighting prodigy.
- Hiya!
A surprise attack. Well done.
That means I win.
I'm the one who cut down
our master. I won.
Now, I believe I said no fighting,
didn't I? You two are friends, right?
Abiru Eisaburo.
He's a bit timid
but that kindness is
the conscience of the Shieikan dojo.
Okay, good boy.
Soji! Eisaburo! The food is ready.
NAGAKURA SHINPACHI
Don't mind me.
Let's go. Okay?
I'm starving!
Sanosuke! Hajime! Heisuke!
Hurry up and eat.
What's this?
Harada Sanosuke.
HARADA SANOSUKE
He loves his food more than anything
and can't stand pointless talk.
Man, this is good.
Greens again? We're pinching pennies, huh?
If you don't want it,
can we give yours to the kids?
They're still growing.
Fine. They can have it.
I've never known anyone who could
wield a sword as masterfully as him.
That's Saito Hajime.
- Then you can have some of mine too.
- Really? Thanks.
Todo Heisuke.
TODO HEISUKE
He's the kindest person you'll ever meet,
but he's also quick to pick a fight.
Are you kidding me?
Yamanami Keisuke is
the most logical of all in the Shieikan.
Don't go wild at mealtime!
Gen, wake up. It's time to eat.
The eldest of us, Inoue Genzaburo...
Wake up! Hey!
INOUE GENZABURO
...is always asleep. Yep.
This will be an easy win.
And who might you be?
Sorry to interrupt your meal.
I'm a traveling medicine salesman.
You folks need anything?
We don't need any! Get outta here!
They say, "Better safe than sorry."
Or have you never heard that one?
What's your problem?
I'm here to challenge your dojo!
Master of the dojo!
Come out!
And the man
who would become the fourth master
of the Tennen Rishin-ryu style.
If you think of the Shieikan
as one big family, he would be its father.
Boss.
A man worthy of the title, Kondo Isami.
Boss. We've got a strange visitor.
KONDO ISAMI
Can't it wait?
Hurry up.
- What's all the fuss?
- This guy has got some nerve.
- He has some nerve.
- That's him. Right there.
You wouldn't happen to be...
the medicine peddler I've heard about
who has been crushing dojos
all over Kanto?
What if I am?
Word is that you're a real handful.
Your name?
From Ishida Village in Tama.
Hijikata Toshizo.
What's the matter?
In a real fight, you'd be dead.
Too many wasted movements.
Don't you dare talk down to me!
That won't get you very far
in a real battle.
This is how you kick.
- Ouch. Boss doesn't hold back.
- Do you think that guy is okay?
You're good!
Finally, after all this time.
Someone who can make me stronger.
If we go on, this could turn deadly.
If I'm not strong enough, I'll die.
That's all there is to it.
Why are you so desperate
to become stronger?
It's my blood.
Your blood?
I can't stop my blood from boiling.
Only when I'm fighting someone strong
do I truly feel alive.
In this day and age
swordsmanship is obsolete.
No matter how strong your sword is,
you can't change this country's course.
Are you an idiot?
What's the fun in doing
the sensible thing?
Doing what no one else can
is what makes you a badass.
I agree.
My apologies.
In that case, I will give it my all.
Yeah!
Don't die on me!
Wait a second!
Gotcha!
Not good enough.
He's okay, right?
I'm sure he's not dead.
Hey.
He's smiling while unconscious.
- You're right.
- That's creepy.
He gave you a tougher time
than expected, didn't he?
It has been a while since I've seen you
get that serious, Kondo.
- Hey.
- Yeah.
I didn't think he had it in him.
This guy might be a good fit for us.
Tennen Rishin-ryu.
A style built for a battle to the death
a practical combat style that requires
facing your foe with complete abandon.
Pretty good, huh?
Here.
In the spring of 1859
Hijikata Toshizo joined
the Tennen Rishin-ryu's Shieikan dojo
at the age of 24.
There.
It was four years
before the Shinsengumi's name
would echo through Kyoto.
SONG OF THE SAMURAI
At the time, the shogunate's real power
was held by the Great Elder, Ii Naosuke.
Ever since the Black Ships arrived,
he strongly advocated for opening Japan.
If we go to war with America,
our country stands no chance of winning.
Even if we cannot
obtain an imperial sanction
we have no other choice
but to sign the treaty!
However, on March 24, 1860
he was killed by ronin from Mito
outside of the Sakuradamon Gate.
Following this, the pro-opening shogunate
and the opposing Sonno Joi faction
were plunged
into an all-out confrontation.
TENNEN RISHIN-RYU SHIEIKAN DOJO
Now's your chance! Go!
I humbly beg your pardon!
Ouch!
Stop!
Naosuke the perv, we took your head!
Naosuke the perv!
It's Naosuke!
- Ii Naosuke. Ke!
- Naosuke the perv! The perv!
998.
999.
1,000!
Hey, Soji.
Yes?
It has been a whole year.
A thousand practice swings.
Every single day, without fail.
Haven't I done enough?
Teach me a move or something!
An actual technique!
If you can complain, you can swing.
Shut up!
How am I supposed to beat our boss
with just practice swings?
The whole reason I joined was to beat him.
Beat the boss, you say?
- Not in a hundred years!
- All right.
I'll teach you a special technique.
- Soji.
- But only if...
you can beat me.
You're on.
Get me a wooden sword.
I'm gonna beat the hell out of you.
I'm fine with this.
Don't you mock me.
This is good.
Ouch. My stomach hurts.
You're laughing too hard.
Come on, this guy spent a whole year
doing 1,000 practice swings
every single day
and he couldn't land a single hit on him.
And to top it all off,
he got his ass kicked with a futon beater!
Basically, that makes you a futon!
A futon!
Well said indeed.
Don't get cocky!
Our match begins now, Hajime!
If you lose to me,
you'll have lost to a futon!
- I'll take you on, you flat futon!
- Who are you calling a flat futon?
Hey, you two, no fighting!
Knock it off! We're eating now.
Let them be. Food and fighting.
Just like a family!
Toshi! Hajime! Stop it already.
Hey, get off me.
Kondo, you're the master of this dojo.
You should have more dignity.
Nameless patriots changed history
in the Sakuradamon Incident.
Doesn't that frustrate you?
I hope we will hear back
about the Kobusho.
The Kobusho?
Still no word, I'm afraid.
Man, don't remind me.
Hey, what is the Kobusho, anyway?
It's the shogunate's official
military academy.
Things have been turbulent
since the Black Ships arrived.
To prepare for the worst
the shogunate established it
to bolster their military forces.
They teach swordsmanship, spearmanship
and even Western-style artillery.
The instructors are the best of the best,
brought in from all across the country.
So it's the ultimate training center,
taught by the strongest guys around.
Kondo is currently running himself ragged
trying to become one of those instructors.
The instructors are first-class,
sanctioned by the shogunate.
Then Shieikan's name
would be recognized as well.
We'll get a stipend
and finally get out of this dump!
And we could teach so many more kids.
That should be a piece of cake
with your skills, Boss.
No, it's not quite that simple.
What do you mean by that?
Either way
at this rate, the Shieikan will
always be just a beat-up old dojo.
Making a name for ourselves will be
nothing more than a pipe dream.
What's this?
Is that about the crossroads slasher?
Oh, the one who has been
popping up lately?
Yeah. There was another incident
about three days ago.
A wooden sword. Do you think
you can challenge me with that?
Don't mess with me, you worthless punk!
He took down Watanabe Noboru,
who had a real sword,
with just a wooden sword?
Is this Watanabe guy any good?
He's the head instructor
of the Shindo Munen-ryu Renpeikan
one of Edo's top three dojos.
To face a master with a wooden sword,
he must be incredibly confident.
All right.
If I take down this slasher bastard,
I'll make a name for the Shieikan.
Interesting.
All right, I'll do it.
Listen to Mr. Flat Futon. Moron!
I agree. I don't think you can do it.
The way you are now, Hijikata,
you couldn't win with 100 attempts.
Soji, you too, you bastard?
That hurt!
That's enough out of all of you! Hey!
Flat futon! That bastard Saito!
And I'm going to crush Soji
one of these days.
I'll take them all down.
You want to take down
the crossroads slasher, right?
Boss.
I'll go with you.
What? If you've just come
to mock me, forget it.
Don't sulk.
So? What's your plan
for finding this slasher?
You're not just going to wander all night
and hope he'll jump you, are you?
I've got a plan for that.
That's him.
What makes you think
he'll be the next target?
Kashiwai Shunsuke is
a master of iai, right?
That slasher bastard has never
fought an iai master, right?
I see.
Pretty clever, Toshi, for you.
Don't be a smartass.
What's this?
You wouldn't happen
to be Kashiwai Shunsuke, would you?
I am.
I request
the honor of a match.
That's him.
I've been waiting for you,
crossroads slasher.
Toshi!
Come! I'll drown you in blood--
You damn crossroads slasher!
I'm Hijikata Toshizo of Tennen Rishin-ryu.
And who the hell are you?
Okada Izo.
You're a crossroads slasher
and you're just going to give me
your name that easily?
It just slipped out. Crap!
Are you from Tosa?
How could you tell?
Your thick Tosa accent
gives you away. Come on!
What is with this guy?
Why you... Okada Izo, brace yourself!
If you come at me all of a sudden,
I can't hold back.
Such speed.
The guy is a monster.
Feel free to run if you want.
Run away?
You can talk trash after you've beaten me,
the strongest man in all of Edo.
The strongest?
You're the strongest?
That's right.
If you claim to be
the strongest man in Edo...
OKADA IZO
...then I just have to beat you
to be the new strongest.
Hey, you! The big guy!
Me?
That sword you have at your hip.
Give it to this man.
I don't want him complaining that he lost
because he didn't have a real blade.
Don't you dare look down on me.
If you're using a wooden sword, so am I.
Is that right? Suit yourself.
What? Are you all talk?
Too close.
Unbelievable!
They're evenly matched.
See? I'm the strongest one here!
No, I am.
Hey, Toshi... Toshi!
You're pretty damn good.
You've got some skills yourself.
Still, why are you out here
slashing people with a wooden sword?
This way,
I don't actually kill my opponents.
And that means I can
fight strong guys over and over.
But if you get cut down, it's over.
Didn't it
ever occur to you
that you could be the one to lose?
No.
But I don't like killing people.
Then why are you doing
this whole slasher thing anyway?
To become
the strongest man there is.
What a coincidence.
Same here.
We'll have another match, Toshizo.
Sure.
I still can't believe it!
Toshi, did you really fight
that crossroads slasher to a draw?
How many times must I tell you? Yes.
Drop the empty bravado.
That's quite petty.
Your comrade went toe-to-toe
with a seriously tough guy.
The least you can do is
give him credit for it.
So, where's the crossroad slasher now?
Who knows?
We said, "We'll have another match,"
and went our separate ways.
What were you thinking?
You found the slasher and just let him go?
Because...
he was a hell of a guy.
I know!
Why don't we have him join us?
With someone that strong,
the Shieikan's name would spread fast.
Wait, didn't you go fight him
to boost our name in the first place?
Oh, right.
Boss, did he really fight that slasher
to a stalemate?
You still don't believe it?
It was just yesterday that Toshi
couldn't score a single point
against Soji with a futon beater.
That's true.
At first, the slasher
had the upper hand, but
gradually, it became an even fight.
Toshi's sword...
may show its true worth only at the limit.
There might be more to that man
than meets the eye.
Oh, the Hiraseigan stance.
Damn it, I was so close!
No, you're mistaken. You were wide open.
Yeah, I know.
Your impatience is
hindering your progress.
Hiraseigan is a dangerous stance
that risks a mutual strike.
Don't rush yourself.
I know, but...
What's up, Eisaburo? Are you
practicing the Hiraseigan stance, too?
I want to master it, too.
Then have Soji teach you.
I already asked him, but he said no.
How come?
He said the Hiraseigan is too dangerous.
Soji only teaches it
to those the boss approves of.
That's why I'll master it myself.
Then have him teach you
a different technique.
No.
It has to be the Hiraseigan.
What do you mean by that?
Because losing is not an option.
Is there someone
you're dying to take down?
Aim!
THE SHOGUNATE KOBUSHO IN EDO
Please!
I beg you.
Please reconsider one more time.
I believe I have told you before.
A farmer's backwater sword style
has no place in our Kobusho.
However many times you come,
my answer won't change!
With all due respect!
Our Tennen Rishin-ryu style
has a proven track record.
- A track record?
- Yes.
The Nikko Toshogu Shrine,
where the divine Lord Ieyasu is enshrined.
Among the Hachioji Sennin Doshin
who serve as its guards
are a great number of
Tennen Rishin-ryu practitioners.
Furthermore, in the registry
by Sanada Hannosuke
the head of the Hokushin Itto-ryu Genbukan
out of the 633 martial artists listed,
64 are from our Tennen Rishin-ryu.
Among the 21 schools in the registry,
ours is the third-most represented.
Besides, the Kobusho
was established by the shogunate
to boost its military power, was it not?
Then there is no style more fitting
than our Tennen Rishin-ryu
which was perfected for actual battle.
Thank you so much, Yamanami!
I can finally become
an official instructor!
Congratulations.
You're finally retainers,
just as you dreamed.
This will make a name
for the Shieikan dojo.
So long, poverty!
We can buy the kids new bamboo swords.
And we'll get more food on the table.
Let's not get ahead of ourselves.
Nothing is official yet.
That may be true,
but we did receive an unofficial offer.
More than anything
your words truly moved me, Yamanami.
Getting our hopes up is a mistake.
It always has been--
Come on, Yamanami.
Just enjoy the moment. You're the one
who made this happen, after all.
You should give yourself
some credit for once.
I don't like it.
What's that?
Got a problem with me? I'm right here.
That's not what I mean.
The one I'm not happy with...
is myself, for not being able
to just enjoy this moment.
You okay there?
Don't overdo it.
Yamanami is a lightweight, you know?
Hey, what the hell is this place?
It's a dump, and it stinks.
- Hey.
- I hate this.
Who the hell are you?
Hey... Hey!
What do you think you're doing,
barging in our dojo with your shoes on?
Oh, my. Was this supposed to be a dojo?
It stank so bad,
I thought it was a cesspool.
- Why you...
- Toshi!
Boss.
My sincerest apologies, Sasaki.
How unexpected. Monkeys have
taken up residence in this cesspit.
Say that again, you son of a bitch!
Stop it. That's Sasaki Tadasaburo.
You don't want to mess with him.
Who the hell is he?
A grandmaster of the Shinto Seibu school.
The finest kodachi user in all of Japan.
He's a master swordsmanship instructor
at the Kobusho.
SASAKI TADASABURO
If we pick a fight,
Kondo's appointment will be off the table.
And...
what might your business be with us?
You have a student here
a punk named Saito Hajime, don't you?
Bring him out.
What has our Saito done?
He cut down Ryunosuke, the firstborn son
of Hatamoto Lord Tajima Yamato-no-Kami.
There must be some kind of mistake.
Yeah, he's right.
Hajime may have a twisted personality,
but he's no murderer.
Get the hell out of here.
No, it's not a mistake.
I'm the one who cut down Tajima Ryunosuke.
Hey, Hajime.
What's the meaning of this?
I didn't like him, so I cut him down.
That's all there is to it.
While Kondo has been humbling himself
for our sakes...
Do you have any idea
what you've just done?
Kondo's...
No.
You're trampling on all of our dreams!
Hey, I don't give a damn
about any of that.
I do what I want, when I want.
That's the only rule I live by.
Besides
I never considered myself
one of your students to begin with.
Hajime.
You're all just so damn annoying.
I'm sick and tired
of your little "happy family" act.
Hey, Hajime!
Say that again, you son of a bitch!
Let's get the hell out of here, old man.
Well, that's just the kind of guy he is.
My condolences.
Hey!
Hijikata.
Eisaburo!
You know something, don't you?
Why did Hajime
kill Tajima Ryunosuke?
Hajime and I...
Before coming to the Shieikan,
we were regulars at an Itto-ryu dojo.
Next!
Hajime!
Ryunosuke.
And Ryunosuke was there, too.
Next!
I'm not done yet!
Ryunosuke loved swordsmanship.
He just couldn't get enough of it.
Not yet!
That was so, even though he was frail
and his father had no faith in him.
Hajime, you are so strong. So strong!
What are you laughing about?
Even so, Ryunosuke didn't give up.
He wanted to be strong, just like Hajime.
Every day, he trained
with that single goal in mind.
But then, the other day, we received word
that Ryunosuke had contracted consumption.
I...
I don't have long to live.
Don't make that face.
Hajime.
I have a favor to ask of you.
What is it?
One last time.
I want to face you in a duel
with real blades.
Are you insane? If you do that, you'll--
I'm going to die anyway!
It's just...
I can't stand it.
To have been born a samurai...
and die having accomplished nothing.
I want some proof
that I truly lived as a samurai.
Good.
You've always pissed me off.
So before you kick the bucket,
I'm going to be the one to kill you.
Hajime.
Stop talking such nonsense!
We can't fight each other!
Eisaburo!
Then what the hell do you think
you're training for?
To spend your whole life here
playing at sword fighting?
I'm not.
And neither is Ryunosuke.
Ryunosuke.
Come at me with everything you've got.
I couldn't stop them.
Because I understood how Ryunosuke felt.
Is that so?
Where do you think you're going?
I'm going to help Hajime. What else?
If you go, you're expelled.
Why?
All Hajime did was
grant his buddy's final wish!
That doesn't give him the right to kill.
I know that!
But you remember
what the boss said, right?
"If we eat together and fight together,
we're family."
Saito killed a man.
That makes him a criminal.
If we help him, Kondo's appointment
as instructor will be revoked.
Finally...
Finally, it's happening.
We've been mocked and dismissed
as country bumpkins with swords.
This is our one chance
to make our name known!
Then expel me.
If we can't even protect our own family
then what's the point
of making a name for ourselves?
Then expel me, too.
If I lose Hajime too,
I won't be able to take it!
Let's go!
Take that!
Is that it?
It doesn't hurt in the slightest.
Ryunosuke put up a better fight than this.
Yeah. If you're going to kill me,
you had better be serious about it.
Thanks for waiting.
Lord Tajima.
This is the man, Saito Hajime.
He's your son's killer.
Please, avenge your son.
Avenge him?
For a samurai heir to be cut down
by some wandering ronin...
is the ultimate disgrace!
Aren't you here to avenge your son?
This is punishment for the dishonor
you've brought upon my family
not for avenging a useless whelp
like Ryunosuke.
Fortunately, my second son, Kotora,
will take over as the family head.
Ryunosuke never had what it takes
to be a leader.
You're the real disgrace here.
What did you just say?
I said you're the disgrace!
You had better watch your mouth.
Even in the state he was in,
Ryunosuke managed to land a blow!
He cut me!
Is that all you've got?
Hajime...
You're afraid of striking me, aren't you?
All you've been doing is dodging!
You're the one who told me
to come at you with everything I had!
Is that it?
Hey!
Is that all the strength
you've got, Ryunosuke?
Ryunosuke! Hey!
Unleash it! Show me everything you've got!
Thank you...
Hajime.
Ryunosuke was magnificent.
He died with more honor as a samurai
than a piece of shit like you ever will.
Shut your filthy mouth, you maggot.
Who are you?
Oh my! Welcome.
Don't get the wrong idea.
I'm not here to save him.
I'm the strongest man in Edo.
You think I can just let that slide?
Who the hell are you?
- Who the hell are they?
- Please stand back.
We will dispose of these annoying flies.
Only two people showed up to help?
You're not very popular, are you?
You idiot. What are you doing here?
You're the real idiot, Hajime,
trying to take this all on yourself.
Just get out of here, now!
Hajime!
So, how do you want to die?
Me? My wish is to die fighting
a strong opponent with all I have.
I'll bet that Ryunosuke kid
felt the same way.
Bring it.
Full of spirit, aren't you?
I like that.
Stay out of this.
This one is mine.
Bring it on!
Ouch!
Guess I have no choice.
Time to settle this.
Hiraseigan?
You...
intend to die here?
Fine by me.
I admire that spirit.
Tennen Rishin-ryu: Sword of No Light!
Looks like things are heating up!
Let me get in on the action!
Boss!
Crashing the party!
What the heck? Did everyone end up coming?
This isn't some casual get-together.
A festival is for everyone
to enjoy, right?
So he's not coming after all?
Boss.
What the hell do you think you're doing?
You son of a bitch!
I'm not your student or anything!
Didn't I already tell you that?
Hajime!
You're right, you're not my student.
You're my precious...
family.
Yamanami?
What gives?
I thought helping meant expulsion.
It's against my better judgment, but...
But I cannot defy the dojo master.
All right.
Now everyone is here.
Let's settle this.
Please wait a moment
Lord Tajima.
Would you please look at this?
It's a note left by your son.
Why do you have this?
Your wife found it and brought it to me.
It says here that your son intended
to face this man in a duel.
This was entirely your son's decision.
If you still refuse to back down...
then we accept your challenge.
Look at all the flies buzzing around.
God, how annoying.
I'm going to kill every last one of you.
That's enough! Stop!
Let's go.
Kondo.
That's the end
of your Kobusho appointment.
It can't be helped.
All this for a stray dog like him?
What a bunch of weirdos.
Let's go.
Yes, sir.
Hajime.
Ouch!
You did well!
That hurts. Boss, that hurts.
Hajime, where do you think you're going?
Thanks to everyone,
they've agreed not to press charges.
Whatever the reason...
I still killed a man.
I can't just pretend it never happened.
I've caused...
Boss and everyone so much trouble.
You're such an awkward man.
I don't want to hear that from you.
See you.
Hajime would later change his name
to Fujita Goro.
The Fujita family's records are said
to state the following,
"Saito Hajime, in his late teens,
killed a man and was forced to leave Edo."
THREE YEARS LATER
That year, coinciding with the 14th shogun
Iemochi's procession to Kyoto
the Roshigumi was formed
to serve as his escort.
Its ranks were filled with ronin,
farmers, and even criminals.
Skilled fighters from all walks of life.
And we of the Shieikan dojo
decided to join their ranks.
I have to say, though.
I never thought we'd be in Kyo,
protecting the shogun himself.
We'll eventually become hatamoto
for the shogun, right?
Talk about moving up in the world!
Hey, Yamanami. I was just thinking.
Why is the shogun going to Kyoto anyway?
The Imperial Court summoned him
to pressure him to expel the foreigners.
Since the Black Ships arrived,
the shogunate's power has been declining.
Basically, the Tokugawa are
losing their grip.
This is a once-in-a-lifetime opportunity
for us!
Kyo is now the heart of Japan!
To test their skills
they say the most famous swordsmen
have gathered there.
Listen up, everyone!
We'll win glory in Kyo
and let the name of the Shieikan
be known across the land!
Bring it on! Let's do it!
So this is Kyo, huh?
It's pretty run-down. I thought
this was supposed to be the capital.
This is very different
from what I had heard.
"Very" is an understatement.
I am Kiyokawa Hachiro!
Gentlemen!
This Roshigumi was formed to escort
the shogun on his procession to Kyoto.
However!
The shogunate is now nothing
but a sinking ship, headed for ruin!
From this day forward
we will serve
as the emperor's personal guard
protect the Imperial Court,
and expel the barbarians!
That is the true calling...
of those loyal to the emperor!
- What the hell is he talking about?
- From now on...
- It seems we've been had.
- our mission is no longer...
- We've been had?
- to guard the shogun...
Kiyokawa intends to use us to expel
foreigners, not to guard the shogun.
But that's treason against the shogunate.
- Rise for the emperor!
- Is that true?
Now is the time to expel the foreigners!
We'll return to Edo!
Edo? Hey! We just got to Kyo!
He's right!
- Ouch! What the hell is your problem?
- Hey, hold it right there.
- Sorry.
- I'm talking to you, bastard!
- A fight?
- Toshi!
Are you going to bump into me
and not say a damn thing?
Are you trying to pick a fight with me,
Araki of Reconnaissance Squad?
Cat got your tongue?
That was close. I almost puked
all the sake I drank yesterday.
Huh? And who the hell are you?
You bastard!
You're dead!
I like this. Pure, unhesitating violence.
I love the energy. Man, I feel sick.
You lot! What do you think
you're doing? Halt!
You're from Mito, aren't you?
What of it?
I was very impressed by the Mito ronin
at the Sakuradamon Incident.
It bolstered my resolve to revere
the emperor and expel them.
They must be your comrades, too.
Don't you wish to change the course
of history, guided by that same will?
No, not interested.
I'm not going back to Edo.
I haven't even gotten laid today.
You bastard! How dare you mock
Master Kiyokawa? Unforgivable!
That's enough!
Hey.
Draw your sword, Kiyokawa.
If it's kill or be killed,
let's go all the way. Right?
That's enough!
Get lost.
Man, you ruined the mood.
Damn it. What a total buzzkill.
Such a buzzkill.
Oh well, nothing to be done.
All right, off to Shimabara with you.
Wait!
Who the hell are you?
You first. Right?
When you ask for a name,
isn't it polite to give your own first?
- Right?
- Hijikata Toshizo.
What?
Hijikata Toshizo!
Well, now, that's interesting. Oh, I see.
I'm Serizawa Kamo.
Favorite word, violence. That's the name.
Later.
Serizawa Kamo.
Man, you have to love Kyo.
If I can scrap with crazy guys like that,
then the trip here was more than worth it.
But what are we going to do?
Kiyokawa is planning
to go back to Edo, right?
Are we going back, too?
It's not that simple.
Huh?
You don't agree with the expulsionists?
There's a more pressing issue.
Whether we head to Edo
or remain here in Kyo
we're short on funds.
What the hell?
Hey, what are you talking about?
I was a fool to think things
would work out
once we reached the capital.
Don't beat yourself up over it.
There's a right and wrong way
to make a name for yourself.
And I don't like Kiyokawa's way
of deceiving people.
We'll just make a name for ourselves
in our own way.
In that case, first things first,
we need to earn our keep.
Yeah. If we can't,
we'll starve in a ditch.
This is where the fun starts.
Please, I'm begging you.
For days, men calling
for the expulsion of foreigners
have been attacking anyone
with ties to the shogunate!
I said get out. Now leave!
Why should I hire
a bunch of nobodies from the sticks?
What the hell? Do you think being
a hatamoto makes you so damn special?
Damn it!
So, we've been turned away again.
Why do you have
to grovel like that to them, Kondo?
There is no use in rushing.
Our funds will only last three more days.
We must find work before then.
Sorry.
ROSHIGUMI QUARTERS
Delicious! I'm so happy!
Hey! You aren't eating at all!
What are you doing?
What the hell do you guys think
you're doing?
Appreciate you stopping by!
What is all this?
We have been exerting ourselves.
Calm down. Come on, have some of this.
Kamo is treating us tonight.
Kamo?
This guy, right here. You know him, right?
Serizawa.
Oh, my. You're quite a large man yourself.
So you're the commander, Kondo Isami?
I've heard the rumors.
I'm honored.
Still, this is just what I would
expect from you, Serizawa.
It must be nice to have such deep pockets.
No, I ain't got any money.
- What?
- Not a penny.
- None.
What are you saying?
Hey, what? What?
What's wrong?
This box had all of our money in it.
There was something in there.
You son of a bitch!
You played us for fools!
Want a piece of me?
That just means you're a moron.
Hey!
You've got a hell of a lot of nerve,
you bastard!
You want a piece of me, asshole?
Knock it off. That's enough.
You all had your fun, didn't you?
Can't really complain now.
Right, Serizawa?
No, I don't think they have to stop.
Flowers, women, and booze are fine,
but isn't something missing?
After all, the one thing that really
gets a man's blood pumping
is good old-fashioned violence,
ain't that right?
Kamo, you're a real piece of work,
you know that?
How about you and I have a go?
No, you don't do it for me.
Right.
I'll take you on instead, Kondo.
For now, let's just call it a night.
What the hell? Talk about an anticlimax.
Kondo Isami of the Tennen Rishin style,
turning tail and running.
I guess it's nothing but
a farmer's hick sword style in the end.
Cut the crap!
Right. And I hear your Shieikan dojo
is a cesspit full of insolent thugs.
No wonder it stinks.
- You son of a bitch!
- Insult Kondo again and I'll...
Cut you down.
Yeah? You gonna try
and cut me down? Can you do that?
I don't know the meaning of holding back.
It's fine. I'm not
very good at that myself.
I like this kid. You've got guts.
You drew your blade.
This is a duel to the death.
I wouldn't have it any other way.
Oume, you just wait right there.
If that's the best you can do,
you're a dead man.
Don't you underestimate me, boy.
I've never seen Soji look like that.
Those eyes. I see. I see now.
You are on this side too.
Bring it on.
Awesome.
I like it.
Man, it's hot.
This place is way too cramped.
It's nice out here.
Flowers and violence.
Okay, I like it.
Yeah, this is a rush.
You're still so green.
Don't push yourself.
Your head is spinning, right?
Serizawa! You are a coward, you bastard!
Fine by me.
There's no honor or cowardice in violence.
The cherry blossoms are falling.
Finally took the bait, huh?
Pull back and you'll lose a finger.
Soji...
lost.
As for his life...
Consider me in your debt.
No.
We're even. I've had my fun.
Now there's a man.
Damn, what a buzzkill.
Sobered me right up.
Boss's hand.
Okita!
Kondo.
I'm sorry.
Next time...
No.
I swear, I'll never lose to anyone again!
That's enough, Soji. You're all right.
You're okay now.
How is Soji?
He has calmed down.
His head injury wasn't anything serious.
Good.
"There's no honor or cowardice
in violence," huh?
That's Serizawa for you.
I've said similar things myself.
But Serizawa and I are different.
That man knows what a real battle is.
A man like that is most terrifying.
Before I knew it, my hands were shaking.
And yet...
I'm dying to fight him.
Stupid, isn't it?
Especially with what Soji
just experienced.
You're an idiot, all right.
But...
I'm excited to see what you'll become.
One who knows oneself grows strong.
So does one who has known defeat.
Knowing defeat, huh?
I don't want to lose.
In those days,
the heart of Japan was the capital, Kyo.
Samurai who were confident in their skill
flocked to the city to test their mettle.
Among them was a man once called a friend.
You bastard! You're a manslayer!
DIVINE RETRIBUTION
Before we knew it, we were swept
into a whirlwind of upheaval.