my Lord Jesus Christ.
Mercy...
... and the power
supported by your might arm .
Brethren,
be strengthened in the Lord
and in the might of His power.
Put on the armor of God
that you might
withstand the devil.
Take unto you
the helmet of salvation
and the sword of the Spirit,
which is the word of God.
As some of you
may be aware, um...
my brother
passed away this week.
And I--I wanted
to thank all of you
who have been so kind
as to send cards and flowers
and-- and even food.
It's greatly appreciated.
Thank you, Father.
Our thoughts are with you,
Father.
God bless you,
your brother,
your whole family.
Thank you, Chester.
Good morning, sister.
Hello, Father.
Oh, Sister...
Would you speak with
Mother Superior
about the um...
There is more
in the common room,
if you have a moment.
Maybe I will.
Your Excellency.
Father.
How are you getting on?
Ah, well, you know,
I'm, I'm...
Yes.
Blessed are those
who mourn,
for they shall be comforted.
This is another transfer?
Hmm. No.
These are
psychiatric reports.
This is a very troubled woman.
Yes. That's the problem.
They haven't found
anything abnormal.
The doctors, I mean.
Well, there--
must be something.
Hissing at the sight
of a church?
That's...
How did this come to you?
They've exhausted
all of the medical,
biological theories.
The woman's parish
wishes to attempt a...
solemn sacrament.
A solemn sacrament,
you mean an exorcism?
And...
you would like me
to perform it?
No. Some poor other soul
already has that distinction.
Oh. And who is that?
Uh, Theophilus Reisinger.
Capuchin from up north,
I believe.
Forgive me,
Your Excellency,
but if the Capuchin
has already been assigned,
why bring this to me?
Well...
they'd like to carry out
the deed here.
Here?
Your Excellency, if--
if this woman
has seen psychiatrists, then
she's, I mean...
clearly...
there must be, uh,
treatment more beneficial
to her than an exorcism.
There are many new remedies
for mental disorders.
I was reading
an article about--
It's all but finalized.
Her address,
number of the transport,
it's right there
in the file.
They're expecting your call.
I understand.
And this is most unusual,
Father,
but the woman is desperate.
She's tried everything else,
but she's been suffering
for years, apparently.
We'll speak with
the Reverend Mother tomorrow,
after the morning Mass
[into phone] Yes,
your manager of operations, please.
One moment.
Thank you.
Yes, hello.
My name is
Father Joseph Steiger.
I'm calling from St. Joseph's
Church in Earling.
We have a passenger who needs
transporting from her home in Marathon.
Do you have service
from Marathon?
Yes, we have.
Good.
What's her name?
Her name is Emma Schmidt.
Miss Schmidt has...
a very sensitive condition
that any unwanted
influence could disrupt,
So, she will need
a private car,
just her and the driver.
And I would appreciate
your discretion.
Yes, St. Joseph's Church
on Olive Street in Earling.
Members of our church
will be here to greet her.
Thank you.
Good day.
She's asleep.
We'll bring her food
when she's awake.
Thank you, Sister.
I must fetch
Father Theophilus.
Oh, are you Father Steiger?
Yes.
Father Theophilus?
Oh, I was just on
my way to the station to meet you.
Oh, well. I was waiting. And then uh--
I'm so sorry I wasn't there to greet you.
- No, no.
- I was detained.
No surprise.
The devil will do
whatever it takes to foil our plans.
We must be ready.
Thank you, Sister.
Thank you.
Oh.
- Father Theophilus.
Reverend Mother...
- Welcome.
- Thank you.
Come in, please.
Have a seat.
So, I've been reading
Emma's files.
Yes.
Some very concerning behavior.
And I am not
entirely convinced
that the problem
isn't psychological.
Well, the task
will be handled
with as little disruption
as possible.
And I thank you,
Reverend Mother,
for allowing us such
a safe space to treat the afflicted.
Thank you.
Mm.
What I need is a team of three in the room
to assist with restraints,
transitions, shorthand.
Father Steiger
will be taking notes,
keeping an accurate
chronology of manifestations and evidences.
We will start
each evening at sundown
and continue until
a pause is needed at my--
I'm sorry.
Sister?
She-- she won't eat.
What's happened, Sister?
I just went in her room
to give her her food
and, um,
she--
she reacted violently.
She...
almost hissed like a cat.
I've never heard
anything like it.
I just--
I don't know.
Has the food been blessed?
I-- I don't--
I don't know.
Bring this to the kitchen.
And have Sister Antonella
prepare it.
Maybe just the rice and beans
from the giveaway.
And, um...
tell her not
to bless the food.
It's all right.
Thank you, Sister.
Good evening, Emma.
I'm Father Steiger.
I'm the parish priest
here at St. Joseph's.
You'll be seeing
quite a bit of me.
You're very welcome here.
Nice to meet you.
Is it your letters?
Mm-hmm.
They're, uh--
to my mother.
You don't see her often?
No.
She-- she passed.
I put them on her grave.
I'm so sorry.
Thank you.
Um...
God bless you.
Goodnight, Emma.
Father Steiger.
Good evening, Father.
How are you settling in?
Oh, wonderful.
You have everything you need?
Yes, thank you.
I'm fine.
Father, uh,
regarding the restraints
you mentioned,
Um, I feel
it might be safer to, uh,
forego them until Emma
can be examined.
Uh--
if her condition is psychological, I feel--
The problem is not
psychological.
Ninety-nine
out of 100 times,
someone contacts the church,
they are assessed,
referred to medical doctors.
And exorcism would
do nothing for them.
This is not that.
Perhaps, uh...
Nevertheless,
I have a childhood friend
who is a medical doctor
in Salem.
He says he can examine
Emma in a week.
I feel we should
forego the restraints until then.
I do believe the restraints will be necessary,
but if you insist.
Thank you, Father.
Goodnight.
Goodnight, Father.
Emma is not well.
I'm sure
that's quite apparent.
She's dehydrated,
malnourished,
tormented.
She suffers on levels
that we ourselves
cannot possibly fathom.
I know this is all unusual,
this aspect of our calling.
It will be like entering a foreign land to you.
So please, I ask you,
follow my instructions,
to the word,
and expect the unexpected.
Spiritually,
emotionally, physically,
though you may be new
to the ways of the enemy,
the enemy's ways are not new.
They're ancient.
It is important
that we work in unison.
The enemy will lie.
He will draw us into sin.
He will do everything
he can to sow discord amongst us.
We are the Lord's army
in this battle.
We are together by His design
to save one of His children.
And to do that,
we must not see
each other as strangers.
For us to be divided,
is for us to fall.
- Are we settled?
- I believe so.
We begin with the Litany.
Holy Mother of God,
Holy Virgin of Virgins,
St. Michael,
St. Gabriel,
St. Raphael,
all holy angels
and archangels,
St. John the Baptist,
St. Peter,
St. Paul,
St. Andrew,
St. James,
St. John,
all holy virgins
all holy saints of God.
Intercede for us.
Be merciful...
Spare us, O Lord.
Graciously hear us,
O Lord.
From
all evil, deliver us, Oh Lord.
From sudden
and unprovided death...
Deliver us, O Lord.
From the snares of the devil...
From lightning and tempest...
Deliver us, O Lord.
From
the scourge of earthquakes...
Deliver us, O Lord.
From everlasting death...
By
the mystery of your holy incarnation;
By your birth...
Deliver us, O Lord.
By your baptism...
By your holy resurrection...
Deliver us, O Lord.
Our Father who art in heaven,
hallowed be thy name,
thy kingdom come,
thy will be done on earth as it is in heaven.
Give us this day
our daily bread;
and forgive us our trespasses
as we forgive those
who trespass against us;
and lead us
not into temptation.
But deliver us from evil.
That's all for today.
Please return her to bed.
See that she is covered.
It will be cold this evening.
Hmm?
Yes, Father.
Emma?
Let's get her...
back into bed.
Thank you, Sisters.
Goodnight, Father.
Oh, Sister Rose...
How was it?
Was there any commotion?
It was fine, Sisters.
Oh, that's all--
I mean, sure, we just--
It was fine.
Excuse me.
Psalm 53.
God, by Your name,
save me,
and by Your might
defend my cause.
God, hear my prayer;
hearken to the words
of my mouth...
For
haughty men have risen up against me,
and fierce men seek my life.
They set not God
before their eyes.
Save me.
God is my helper.
The Lord sustains my life.
Turn back the evil
upon my foes.
In your faithfulness,
destroy them.
Freely will I offer you sacrifice.
I will praise your name,
Lord in Jesus' name.
Save your servant.
All who trust in you, my God.
Let her find in you, Lord,
a fortified tower.
In the face of the enemy.
Father?
And let the enemy
have no power over her.
And the son
of inequity be powerless to--
Harm her.
Father?
Oh, no.
That shouldn't be.
Sisters, please.
Please?
Sisters!
Emma?
Back to the chair, please.
Oh, no.
Please.
Emma! Father?
Please, Emma!
Emma, please.
Emma, no! Father!
Are you going to
repent, Father?
Stop!
Are you going to repent?!
Father?
Father, please.
- No! Emma--
- Father?
No, Emma!
No, no!
Stop, Emma!
No!
Father,
what happened tonight,
it cannot be allowed.
You and I,
we have to--
She cannot be
permitted just to grab at a sister--
She must be restrained, Father.
I know this is new
territory for you and the sisters.
My concern
about restraining her
- was out of consideration--
- No, no,
we'll ensure
it's done safely
for her protection and ours.
Please, I've done this before.
Let the young sister rest.
Another will stand
in her place tomorrow.
It's the only way, Father.
Yeah. I hope you're right,
Father.
Reverend Mother.
You wanted to see me?
Yes, Emma.
What's happening with her?
Is-- is progress occurring or?
Progress, yes. Uh...
That might be a better
question for Father Theophilus.
The medical report states
that a portion
of Sister Rose's scalp
was torn from her head.
It's right here.
Sister.
Hello, Father.
How are you feeling?
Um...
Oh, the, um...
doctor in Kirkman today,
he gave me some ointment
and a softer bandage.
Good. May I?
Yes, please.
Sister, I am so sorry.
I...
Going forward,
she will be restrained.
Perhaps she should have been,
from the start.
That is my fault.
I can only apologize.
Father, I know that
she is profoundly ill
and not under her own control.
But...
despite myself,
I was angry at her.
Asking myself
if God is punishing her
or if she's punishing us
for something.
I don't know.
I've never
felt such bitterness.
And I'm ashamed.
Sister, this is
a profoundly new
and strange situation
for all of us.
You are entitled
to your feelings
and you have nothing
to be ashamed of.
Um, Father, will you...
Of course.
Thank you, Father.
I hope you continue
to feel better.
Sister?
The sooner we do this,
the sooner it's over.
All right.
I'm hurt.
Let us pray.
God, whose nature is
ever merciful and forgiving,
accept our prayer
that this servant of yours
may be pardoned
by your loving kindness,
Holy Lord,
Almighty Father,
everlasting God,
and Father
of our Lord Jesus Christ,
Unnnnnngggg.
who once and for all consigned
that fallen
and apostate tyrant
to the flames of hell.
She's seizing.
Keep her head turned.
Careful, watch her legs...
Father,
this is a seizure.
Head towards you.
Stay back.
Therefore, I adjure you
every unclean spirit,
every specter from hell,
every satanic power
in the name
of Jesus Christ of Nazareth
to cease your assaults
against the creature
who He has formed
in his own honor and image.
I command you, unclean spirit,
along with all your minions,
now attacking
this servant of God
by the ascension
of our Lord Jesus Christ
that you tell me by some sign,
your name--
and the day and hour
of your departure.
It places the filth
in the corner.
Speak plainly
and answer me now.
All in this
room are full of sin.
Enough distractions!
The Father, the Son,
the Holy Spirit.
Oh, Father...
Father,
I need to speak with you.
What happened this evening
with the ritual...
How could you just--
- How is she--
- No, no, no.
It wasn't her, Father.
- What?
- It wasn't her.
Yes, but the symptoms
she was exhibiting,
it seems to be almost--
almost like an epilepsy,
but there's no record
of this in the files.
Father, our job is
to protect the afflicted
without giving the enemy
any more advantage
than is necessary.
Sometimes that will require
remaining in the dark
about certain things.
There is more
to Heaven and Earth
than is even dreamt of
in our philosophy.”
Hamlet, Shakespeare.
Good night, Father.
When
time began, the Word was there
and the Word was God.
And without Him,
there came to be not one thing
that has come to be.
In Him was life,
and the life
was the light of men.
She needs a bucket.
Fetch a bucket.
Rid yourself
of that vile weed.
Who speaks to us?
First,
remove the chaplet.
Remove the chaplet!
No one here
carries a chaplet.
Bring
that to the chapter house,
and then you can return,
Sister.
Now who speaks to us?
How is your brother, Father?
Tell me who you are!
He still hanging
on by a thread?
Quiet!
Tell me your name!
Your name!
I am Mina,
and if you do that again
you will eternally regret it!
Tell me why have
you chosen to torment this servant of God?
She needs help.
Emma?
Come in.
Sister.
Oh. Uh--Father,
I'm... I'm sorry.
I didn't, um...
No, it's quite all right.
Um-- please.
I, uh, I just...
What are these?
Did she do those?
Yes.
"What will you give me
if I deliver him
over to you?"
Is that Judas?
Emma?
Ohh!
Oh, fetch, uh, warm clothes.
Not too hot.
And, uh, extra pillows.
Father,
what are we doing?
This is getting out of hand,
look at her.
She's in a dire state.
- Yes.
- We are making it worse.
- No.
- There was--a medical doctor
coming to see her on Monday.
Why don't we just wait
until he--
Wait, wait, wait.
That's just what
they want us to do is wait.
But we must continue.
Because if
we are inconsistent,
their grasp will
harden like cement.
They'll devour her and you and me and all of us.
I just think
with her in this state-
Enough!
If you do not want
to participate, Father
I accept your withdrawal.
The enemy will be delighted with your absence.
Uuuunnngngngngnng...
Emma, Emma.
Emma, poor child.
We're going to soothe you.
Do not fear,
for I am with you.
We must begin.
Almighty Lord,
Word of God,
the Father of Jesus Christ,
God and Lord of all creation;
who along with the other
mandates to work miracles
was pleased to grant them
the authority to say:
"Depart, you devils!"
And by whose might
Satan was made to fall
from heaven like lightning;
I ask this through
you, Jesus Christ,
the living and the dead and the world by fire.
Her light will soon be extinguished.
By
whom is her light being extinguished?
Satan will soon crush
the God of peace
under your feet.
Cease with your diversions!
And tell me
to whom I speak.
I have
sinned in that I have betrayed
the innocent blood.
You are Judas?
Why are you tormenting
this poor soul?
So she rots from the inside
and slaughters
herself like a pig!
You want her
to take her own life.
And who else
haunts this woman?
Father--
- Father!
- Silence!
Unclean spirits!
Now haunting this woman,
give me your name!
See the cross of the Lord
and reveal yourself!
Reveal yourself!
The restraint!
- Sister!
Emma! Come!
I can't lift her.
Oh, my hand,
my hand!
Emma!
My hand!
All right, enough!
Everybody out now!
Out!
I have uh, a sister with a torn scalp.
I now somehow have one with a crushed hand.
Am I to stand by
while she harms another?
What is happening in there?
How are we helping her?
She needs a--
a doctor,
medical attention
or something.
Do you have trouble seeing,
Father?
Excuse me?
It's clearly
you're not seeing
what is happening in there,
what's coming out
of this girl.
You're still
looking for some...
rational, modern explanation.
This has existed for eternity.
I can see perfectly clearly
that this girl
is deteriorating.
And my job here, Father,
is to care for this parish and those within it.
And I cannot simply sit
there while you drive this--
Your task is to take notes.
You don't understand this.
You don't understand
these devils.
- It's very clear to me.
- What devils are you talking about?
You have your theories,
you have your research,
you have your reports,
but you don't understand the enemy. You don't.
What if you're wrong?
What if what she really needs
is a doctor?
is a psychiatrist?
Trust me, Father.
We are paying a price
for your lack of faith.
- For my lack of faith?
- Yes.
How dare
you stand there and-- and say that my doubts
are causing what is
happening to this poor girl!
Because that is exactly what
happened in Redding!
What are you talking about?
What happened in Redding?
The ritual happened there!
I was called to perform it.
Emma and her mother,
they were desperate.
Wait a minute,
wait a minute,
You knew Emma
as a young girl?
Yes.
You didn't think to tell us?
You didn't think
that might be information
that could be useful to us?
Why is that not
in Emma's file?
This is what I'm
talking about, Father.
All these mystical,
cryptic sayings.
You drip-feeding us
information as you see fit.
This has to end, Father, now!
All right.
You want information?
Yes.
I'll give it.
For your sake.
Sit.
Listen to me, Father.
When I first came to Redding,
I had just recently
become an exorcist.
I had felt I had
the calling, but I was unschooled.
I didn't have the tools.
Those assisting me
were uneducated too.
We couldn't cope
with what was happening
but we knew
she was possessed.
We abandoned her.
We surrendered her over
to the doctors.
And she herself,
like a miracle,
wrote me letters,
said she recovered.
She finished school.
She found a passion
for service, of course.
These devils,
these deceivers,
they were biding their time
inside her,
waiting for
the perfect moment.
And then it came.
When her mother died,
that gave them
the opportunity
to seize their chance.
Why Emma?
Why would they
snatch her life away?
Why not--
somebody else?
Emma is a different
kind of person, Father.
She's a person of
profound sensitivity.
She is touched by
something otherworldly.
And with that kind of
vulnerability, that openness,
any wound like trauma,
neglect,
involvement in the dark arts,
everything that she was
exposed to as a child,
that's what allows
these invasions to occur.
To take root.
To degrade you.
To debase you.
And do the same to those around you Us, Father.
We are the targets too.
Their goal is to make us
give up on God.
I really said too much
to you, Father.
Now even you are susceptible.
So please,
for all our sake,
we must continue.
We cannot abandon Emma
like this.
No.
I abandoned her once,
not again.
Emma?
"Amongst
the hardships Emma experienced
were the consistent rumors
and subsequent proof
that her father Jacob
and her mother's sister, Mina
entered into an illicit
relationship
and attempted to
confound Emma using...
witchcraft.
On several occasions,
Jacob and Mina
reportedly fed Emma food
which had been cursed
including fruit, baked
potatoes and tobacco leaves."
Father,
there's something you need to see.
What did you do?
I don't
understand what is happening here.
Whatever this is
that you are doing,
it is failing.
The sisters are traumatized.
No one is sleeping.
Everyone for miles is--
is frightened and suspicious.
I want to shut this down.
I want to shut
this whole thing down.
I will give you one more week.
And if it is not over by then,
this whole
whatever this is must end.
We need to get back
to our lives
and leave all of this behind.
I wish it to be over too,
Reverend Mother,
but I'm sure that the devil
does not bend
to our calendar.
It will bend or don't bend.
It will not be
under this roof.
And I'm moving Emma
to the cellar.
What? The cellar?
Is there even heat down there?
Those rooms have been
out of use for years.
It's done.
She is too dangerous,
too volatile.
This will be better for her.
It's more private
and more secure.
Father, can you excuse us, please?
I need to talk to
the leader of our parish.
Of course, Reverend Mother.
Father Steiger.
Father, you don't look well.
If I didn't know better,
I would say
that you are losing control
of this situation.
You have invited something
into this community
that no one understands.
And everyone, including you,
is starting to be--
Please, Reverend Mother,
please let me do my job.
This is my parish.
It is my responsibility.
And while I am grateful
for your concern,
I do not need to be
watched over.
Thank you.
Father,
All my life I have been
taking direction from men.
Men who are
not as smart as me,
not as disciplined,
and whose piety
pales in comparison
to the women of this convent.
I thought you were different.
But now...
perhaps we do need someone
who can provide the parish
with more stability.
Perhaps you're right,
Reverend Mother.
She's malnourished and dehydrated,
but I don't see any infection
on the lesions
and the facial swelling
will go down.
She just needs rest.
They're keeping her alive.
They're feeding off her.
There's something going on
inside of her
and it's affecting all of us.
Something is happening here
and she...
I-- I-- I don't know.
Just get as much
food and water in her as possible
and if you see any signs
of infection, send word.
Take care of yourself, Joe.
There's evil in the church!
Father,
you gotta do something!
Great God in Heaven,
that poor poor creature...
Her condition,
is this how it started?
No, no.
When she first arrived,
she was uh,
she was very thin and, uh,
there were scratches,
but nothing...,
nothing like this.
And the doctor says
there's no basis for committing her.
Committing her?!
Uh, well, I--
I-- I don't know.
Um...
what I do know is
that she continues to worsen
and if we do nothing,
if we-- if she receives
no medical attention,
then she is almost
certainly going to...
What?
- Well, almost certainly--
- She's going to what?
She's going to die!
- Okay. Calm down!
The last thing
this parish needs
is a priest
breaking down outside.
I know that brother's passing
weighs heavily on you,
but you are the parish
priest and you need to lead.
Yes,
Your Excellency.
Good.
Hello, Father
Sister. Please.
I was just preparing
for tonight's ritual,
so Sister Mary can rest.
Preparing?
Can I ask you a question?
Have you ever felt alone?
I just...
I was trying to pray
the Vespers and...
it didn't feel like anyone
was listening.
Well...
I wish I could
offer you some...
salient wisdom,
but the truth is...
the truth is...
I don't know what I'm doing.
How is your head?
Uh...
It's fine.
I-- I should go.
Holy Lord,
Almighty Father,
everlasting God and Father
of our Lord Jesus Christ,
who once and for all consigned
that fallen and apostate
tyrant to the flames of hell,
who sent your only
begotten Son into the world
to crush that roaring lion
Strike terror, Lord, into--
What?!
Father, we have to stop.
- Father, please.
- Please stop.
- What? No!
- Father, we can't.
Father, please.
Fill your servants
with courage to fight
mentally against
that reprobate dragon.
Can you feel
her touch, Father?
Her skin against yours?
Next time
he tries to fuck you
you better open wide,
you stupid whore!
Almighty Lord,
Word of God
the Father of Jesus Christ,
God and Lord of all creation,
Why are you leaving
your post so soon, Father?
Who gave
to your holy apostles--
There's a little extra
rope for you right up there.
Serpents and scorpions.
Perhaps you can
join your dear departed brother!
Shut up! Shut up!
You don't know what
you're talking about.
I can't take it, Father.
This has to stop, Father.
This has to stop!
- I can't take it anymore!
- Hey! Just get out!
Catch your breath.
I can't take it anymore!
Go!
I humbly call
on your holy name,
in fear and trembling,
asking that you grant me
your unworthy servant,
pardon for all my sins...
And
the power supported by your mighty arm.
I--I can't hold...
No, no, no, no.
We have to turn her.
Turn her on her side!
Emma? Emma?
She would be dehydrated.
She needs to
replenish her fluids.
Yes, Father.
She shall
bask in the infernal kingdom
of hell for eternity.
In the name
of the Lord Jesus Christ,
Emma, can you hear me?
Emma, Emma.
Here, sit.
There, it's okay.
Aaaah!
Her suffering shall be
laid at your feet.
How--
how did you find us?
If you continue,
your days left
on Earth will be few.
Sister Rose?
Sister Rose!
Father?
Aaaaaaah!
Father Steiger...
Father, I don't know
what's happening.
Why?
Please, come in.
Come in.
I'm sorry, I feel like I'm
being drawn into something
and I-- I can't eat
I can't sleep,
I can't think, Father,
I can't think.
Ohh!
Yeah. Yeah.
Sit-- Sit down, Father
And Emma, Father.
Emma, she--
she haunts me, Father.
She haunts me.
How did she know?
How does Emma know
of my brother?
My brother, Father.
He...
He took his own life, Father.
A month ago,
he took his own life.
He was in so much pain
He was in so much
pain, Father.
And none of us knew.
None of us knew
until it was too late
and he was crying out
and I couldn't help him
because I was so preoccupied.
I was caught up in myself
in this stupid place.
Please, sit.
Sit.
I'm sorry, Father.
I have no use.
Here, Drink this.
It'll help
Thank you.
Thank you, Father.
This is the enemy's mission,
to make us doubt ourselves,
God, our purpose on earth,
and most important:
cause us suffering.
I had a sister, you know.
Claire.
Disease was all over Europe.
Cholera, small pox, polio.
I was old enough.
I survived,
but many didn't.
After we lost Claire,
all the pain continued
for years.
Bigotry, censorship,
rising fascism
you name it...
Most of my family
succumbed to the turmoil.
It's what brought me here
to this country years ago.
And that's what brought me
to my calling.
Your calling.
You understand, Father?
This grief,
all this suffering,
Job's in the desert,
Joan of Arc, yours, mine,
your brother's,
Emma's, everybody's.
It may look bleak,
but these trials,
these temptations,
they fortify us
for a greater good.
To grow into those
we are destined to be.
Our raison d'etre .
Raison d'etre?
Yes.
I thought I was just
supposed to be taking notes.
I'm just making
things worse, Father.
You're not a spectator,
Father.
You are a priest.
You must understand
your own importance, please.
Your faith, your intelligence, your commitment.
I don't understand my faith.
Remember, Father,
Emma had no one.
No parish wanted
any part of her.
They wouldn't touch her.
Yet you...
and the Reverend Mother
and the sisters,
you all accepted this task
like great warriors.
Because when the word
of the Lord is spoken
through us,
with commitment and passion,
even Satan must listen.
Like Saint Michael
defending the glory of God
in battle.
It's the most powerful
weapon we have.
I found a Saint Michael
medallion
in my brother's things.
I was... looking through them the other night.
My brother's name
was Michael.
Ah!
What?
Hmm?
So I, uh,
I wrote this letter...
before I came.
Would you place it
on my mother's grave
in Redding,
please?
- You will place it there
yourself, not me, Emma.
You're holding on
too tight, Father.
I won't hear of it, Emma.
It's too deep.
Please.
I owe it to you.
I owe it to my mother.
It's too deep.
It's cold.
Emma's condition is dire.
These devils,
they found their way
into her core,
her sinew.
So once we begin tonight,
we can't stop.
Because if we let up or
give the enemy time to mend,
we will lose her forever.
So if you need a moment
to rest, go.
If you need water,
food or fresh air,
take respite.
We must be resolute
because we are the ones
that stand in the breach.
And hold back the darkness.
Even if it means we
don't come back from it.
Attention Beelzebub,
and all manner of brutes
and hellions
tormenting this woman.
Cami...
In
the name of the Father and of the Son,
my little Camila...
and of the Holy Spirit.
help me, please...
Let your mighty hand
cast him out of Your servant--
Grandma?
They are torturing me
So he may no longer hold...
Sister, do not listen.
Please help me.
I can't take it.
[in
Spanish] Grandma, forgive me.
Sister!
Jesus would never allow
my beautiful
grandmother's voice
into a lying snake like you.
You won't fool me,
you vile beast!!!
Abandon your own grandmother?
You'll rot in hell,
you stupid fucking bitch!
Let go of me!
Help!
Their little cries.
I drowned them,
one by one,
each one screamed more
than the last.
The sounds of their gasps
were like music in my ears.
And Jesus was laughing
right along with me.
Leave this servant of God!
And be gone!
Thank you,
Reverend Mother.
Let your Sisters be cut,
bruised and degraded?
How could you
let this happen?
You've destroyed
their spirits.
Their spirits will never be destroyed.
They're too strong
for you.
Sister!
What happened?
She was just--
I don't know,
I never--
she just came across like a...
What happened?
Where is she?
She's in the catacombs.
Tell everyone else
to get into their rooms.
Yes, Father.
What is happening?
Emma's escaped...
- Where did she go?
- The catacombs, I think...
Just go!
Go!
I'll tell the sisters.
Sisters, come!
Come quickly
to my chambers!
Emma?
It's alright.
Come, we'll be safer
in here.
Come, quickly.
Quickly.
Emma?
Ahh!
Father,
You have failed her.
Mother?
Yes, it's alright.
It's alright.
She's here.
I found her!
Emma?
Sister?
Where's Father Theophilus?
I, uh--
We found her!
She's here.
She's not breathing.
Father?
She's--
I don't know.
Check for bleeding.
There's no sign of blood.
She's not breathing.
Her pulse is--
is very faint.
No, no. She can't die.
She can't die.
Emma?
Emma speak to us.
Something is
blocking her breath.
We need to get her up.
Okay sister,
we need more light.
Emma?
Wake up.
She already belongs to us!
Call to her.
It is through
the devil I speak now.
It is God himself
who commands you.
God the Father commands you.
God the Son commands you.
God the Holy Spirit
commands you.
It is He who commands you.
He who once stilled the sea
and the wind and the storm!
Hearken, therefore,
and tremble in fear, Satan,
you enemy of the faith,
you foe of the human race.
See the light, Emma!
See the light!
You corrupter of justice,
you root of all evil and vice;
you begetter of death,
you robber of life!
You are guilty,
before Almighty God,
guilty before His Son,
guilty before
the whole human race.
He who is coming to judge
both the living and the dead
and the world by fire!
Emma!
Look at the light, Emma!
Depart, Jacob.
Depart, Mina.
Depart, Judas.
Betrayer of Jesus Christ!
Depart, Asmodeus,
Sathanas,
Leviathan, Beelzebub,
And all Princes of Hell
within this servant of God,
depart!
Depart!
Emma...
Don't let go.
Hear the voice of God.
Hear us.
Here,
Come.
Come, be careful.
Our Father,
who art in heaven,
hallowed be Thy name.
Thy kingdom come.
Thy will be done
on earth as it is in heaven.
Emma, Emma.
I have you.
Saint Michael the Archangel,
illustrious leader
of the heavenly army
defend us in the battle
against principalities
and powers against the rulers
of the world of darkness.
Holy Mary,
Mother of God pray for us sinners,
now and at the hour
of our death. Amen.
Behold the handmaid
of the Lord:
Be it done unto me
according to Thy word.
We carry our prayers up
to God's throne
that the mercy of the Lord
may quickly come
and lay hold of the Satan
and his demons,
casting him into chains,
into the abyss,
so that he can no longer
seduce the nations.
He has cast you forth
into the outer darkness
where everlasting ruin awaits.
You are guilty before His Son,
our Lord Jesus Christ,
whom you dared to nail
to the cross.
You are guilty before
the whole human race,
to whom you proffered
by your enticements
the poisoned cup of death.
Therefore, I adjure you,
profligate dragon,
in the name
of the spotless Lamb,
to depart this woman
and to depart from
the church of God.
Emma?
Hi, Emma.
Emma.
Is it over?